<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><document><enww><home1 type="content"><title>Animated Getting Started Guide</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>This animated getting started guide shows how to install and set up your new HP LaserJet product.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Select your product below</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB install</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Wireless install</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 and P1600 Printer Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB install</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Network install</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Home</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Install Printer Software</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» View User Guide</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series USB install</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series wireless install</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series USB install</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series network install</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Begin Setup</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Select a sturdy, well-ventilated, dust-free area, away from direct sunlight to position the product.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Remove all orange shipping tape and protective plastic.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Open the print cartridge door. Remove the foam block, print cartridge, discovery sheet, and attached orange shipping lock. <b>NOTE:</b> Recycle the foam block, discovery sheet, and shipping lock.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Remove the orange shipping lock from the end of the print cartridge. Rotate the print cartridge front to back to distribute the toner evenly. Pull the tab to remove the toner tape. <b>NOTE:</b> Recycle the shipping lock and toner tape.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Install the toner cartridge in the product and close the print cartridge door.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Adjust the paper guides and load paper face-up in Tray 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Plug in the power cord. <b>NOTE:</b> Record the model number, product number, and serial number for product registration.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Turn on the product.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Start the software installation and follow the on-screen instructions.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>To install a wireless model, refer to the <em>Windows Wireless Installation</em> section in the <b>Getting Started Guide</b>, or refer to the <em>Install the product on a wireless network</em> section in the <b>User Guide</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Install the output bin as shown here.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Install the dust cover.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Connect the network cable to the product. Verify that one of the network lights is illuminated on the network port located on the back of the product.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Wait about four minutes for the network to assign an IP address for the product, and then print a configuration page from the product control panel. To print the page, press and hold the <b>Go</b> button, and then release the button when the ready light begins blinking. Locate the IP address in the <em>Network Information</em> section.</p></string8b></enww><arww><home1 type="content"><title>دليل بدء الاستخدام المتحرك</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>.الجديد وإعداده HP LaserJet يعرض دليل بدء الاستخدام المتحرك هذا كيفية تثبيت منتج</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>حدد منتجك أدناه</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>USB تثبيت «</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>التثبيت اللاسلكي «</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>P1600 Printer Series و HP LaserJet Pro P1560</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>USB تثبيت «</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>التثبيت من شبكة الاتصال «</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>الصفحة الرئيسية  «</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>تثبيت برنامج الطابعة  «</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>عرض دليل المستخدم  «</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series الخاص بـ USB تثبيت</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series التثبيت اللاسلكي الخاص بـ </prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series الخاص بـ USB تثبيت</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>من شبكة الاتصال HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series تثبيت</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>بدء الإعداد «</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>.اختر مكاناً ثابتاً، تتم تهويته بشكل جيد، وخالياً من الغبار، وغير معرّض لأشعة الشمس المباشرة لتضع فيه المنتج</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>.انزع كافة أشرطة الشحن البرتقالية إضافةً إلى الواقي البلاستيكي</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>.افتح باب خرطوشة الطباعة.انزع حاجز الفوم وخرطوشة الطباعة وورقة الاكتشاف إضافةً إلى قفل الشحن البرتقالي المرفق.قم بإعادة تدوير حاجز الفوم وورقة الاكتشاف وقفل الشحن <b>:ملاحظة</b>  </p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>.انزع قفل الشحن البرتقالي من طرف خرطوشة الطباعة.قم بتدوير خرطوشة الطباعة بحيث يتوزع مسحوق الحبر بشكل متساوٍ.اسحب اللسان لإزالة شريط مسحوق الحبر.قم بإعادة تدوير قفل الشحن وشريط مسحوق الحبر <b>:ملاحظة</b></p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>.ثبّت خرطوشة الحبر في المنتج ثم أغلق باب خرطوشة الطباعة</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>.قم بضبط موجهات الورق وبتحميل الورق مع مراعاة وضع وجه الطباعة نحو الأعلى في الدرج 1</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>.قم بتوصيل سلك الطاقة.سجّل رقم الطراز ورقم المنتج والرقم التسلسلي لتسجيل المنتج <b>:ملاحظة</b></p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>.شغّل المنتج</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>.ابدأ بتثبيت البرنامج واتبع الإرشادات التي تظهر على الشاشة</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>في <em>Windowsالتثبيت اللاسلكي لـ </em> لتثبيت طراز لاسلكي، راجع قسم     <em>تثبيت المنتج على شبكة لاسلكية</em> أو راجع قسم ،<b>دليل بدء الاستخدام</b>                                                             .<b>دليل المستخدم</b> في</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>.قم بتثبيت حاوية الإخراج كما هو موضح هنا</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>.قم بتثبيت غطاء الغبار</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>.قم بتوصيل كابل الشبكة بالمنتج.تأكد من إضاءة أحد مصابيح شبكة الاتصال على منفذ الشبكة الموجود في الجزء الخلفي من المنتج</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>.للمنتج، ثم اطبع صفحة تكوين من لوحة التحكم بالمنتج IP انتظر حوالي أربع دقائق ريثما تعيّن الشبكة عنوان.ثم حرره عندما يبدأ المصباح بالوميض <b>(تشغيل) Go</b> لطباعة الصفحة، اضغط باستمرار الزر.<em>معلومات الشبكة</em> في قسم IPحدد موقع عنوان</p></string8b></arww><bgww><home1 type="content"><title>Анимирано ръководство за начално запознаване</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Това анимирано ръководство за начално запознаване демонстрира как да инсталирате и настроите вашия нов принтер HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Изберете вашето устройство по-долу</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Инсталация чрез USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Безжична инсталация</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 и P1600 Printer Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Инсталация чрез USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Мрежова инсталация</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Начало</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Инсталиране на софтуера на принтера</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Преглед на ръководството за потребителя</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Инсталация чрез USB на HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Безжична инсталация на HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Инсталация чрез USB на HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Мрежова инсталация на HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Начало на инсталацията</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Изберете стабилно, добре проветрявано и незапрашено място, настрани от пряка слънчева светлина, където да поставите принтера.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Отстранете всички оранжеви транспортни ленти и пластмасовите вложки.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Отворете вратичката за печатащата касета. Извадете блока от стиропор, печатащата касета, защитния лист и включения оранжев фиксатор за транспортиране. <b>ЗАБЕЛЕЖКА:</b> Предайте за рециклиране блока от стиропор, защитния лист и фиксатора за транспортиране.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Премахнете оранжевия фиксатор за транспортиране от края на печатащата касета. Завъртете печатащата касета напред-назад, за да разпределите тонера равномерно. Дърпайте езичето, за да отстраните лентата на тонера. <b>ЗАБЕЛЕЖКА:</b> Предайте за рециклиране фиксатора за транспортиране и лентата на тонера.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Поставете касетата с тонера в принтера и затворете вратичката на касетата.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Регулирайте водачите за хартията и заредете хартията с лицевата страна надолу в тава 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Включете захранващия кабел. <b>ЗАБЕЛЕЖКА:</b> Запишете номера на модела, номера на устройството и серийния номер за регистрация на продукта.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Включете принтера.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Започнете инсталирането на софтуера и следвайте инструкциите на екрана.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>За да инсталирате безжичен модел, направете справка в раздела <em>Безжична инсталация на Windows</em> в <b>Ръководство за начално запознаване</b> или в раздела<em>Инсталиране на устройството в безжична мрежа</em> в <b>Ръководство за потребителя</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Инсталирайте изходната тава, както е показано тук.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Поставете калъфа против прах.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Свържете мрежовия кабел към принтера. Уверете се, че един от индикаторите за мрежата свети за мрежовия порт в задната част на устройството.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Изчакайте около четири минути, докато мрежата присвои IP адрес на устройството, и след това отпечатайте страница с конфигурацията от контролния панел на устройството. За да отпечатате страницата, натиснете и задръжте бутона <b>Старт</b>, и го отпуснете, когато лампичката за готовност започне да мига. Намерете IP адреса в раздела <em>Мрежова информация</em>.</p></string8b></bgww><caww><home1 type="content"><title>Guia animada de primers passos</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Aquesta guia animada de primers passos descriu com instal·lar i configurar el vostre producte HP LaserJet nou.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Seleccioneu el vostre producte a continuació</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Impressora HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instal·lació per USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instal·lació sense cables</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Impr. HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1560 i P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instal·lació per USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instal·lació per xarxa</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Inici</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instal·la el programari de la impressora</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Consulta la Guia de l’usuari</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instal·lació per USB de l'HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instal·lació sense cables de l'HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instal·lació per USB de l'HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instal·lació sense cables de l'HP LaserJet Pro sèrie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Comença la instal·lació</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Seleccioneu una superfície estable, ben ventilada, sense pols i allunyada de la llum del sol directa per situar el producte.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Traieu tota la cinta adhesiva d’embalatge taronja i el plàstic protector.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Obriu la porta del cartutx d'impressió. Traieu el bloc d'escuma, el cartutx d'impressió, la làmina i el blocatge de transport taronja. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicleu el bloc d'escuma, la làmina i el blocatge de transport.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Traieu el blocatge de transport taronja de l'extrem del cartutx d'impressió. Gireu el cartutx d'impressió de davant cap enrere per tal que el tòner es distribueixi uniformement. Tireu de la pestanya per retirar el precinte del tòner. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicleu el blocatge de transport i el precinte del tòner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Inseriu el cartutx de tòner al producte i tanqueu la porta del cartutx d'impressió.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Ajusteu les guies del paper i carregueu el paper cara amunt a la safata 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Endolleu el cable d'alimentació. <b>NOTA:</b> Anoteu el número de model, el número de producte i el número de sèrie per registrar el producte.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Engegueu el producte.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Inicieu la instal·lació del programari i seguiu les instruccions de la pantalla.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Per instal·lar un model sense cables, consulteu la secció <em>Instal·lació sense cables del Windows</em> de la <b>Guia d'instal·lació</b> o la secció <em>Instal·lació del producte en una xarxa sense cables</em> de la <b>Guia de l'usuari</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Instal·leu la safata de sortida com s'indica.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Instal·leu la sobrecoberta.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Connecteu el cable de xarxa al producte. Comproveu que un dels indicadors lluminosos de xarxa estigui encès al port de xarxa situat a la part posterior del producte.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Espereu uns quatre minuts perquè la xarxa assigni una adreça IP per al producte i, a continuació, imprimiu una pàgina de configuració des del tauler de control del producte. Per imprimir la pàgina, mantingueu premut el botó <b>Endavant</b> i, a continuació, deixeu-lo anar quan l'indicador lluminós a punt comenci a parpellejar. Localitzeu l'adreça IP a la secció <em>informació de xarxa</em>.</p></string8b></caww><csww><home1 type="content"><title>Animovaná příručka Začínáme</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Tato animovaná příručka Začínáme ukazuje, jak nainstalovat a nastavit nové zařízení HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Vyberte své zařízení</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB instalace</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Bezdrátová instalace</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1560 a P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB instalace</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Síťová instalace</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Domovská stránka</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalace tiskového softwaru</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Zobrazit uživatelskou příručku</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1100 – USB instalace</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1100 – bezdrátová instalace</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 – USB instalace</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Řada HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 – síťová instalace</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Zahájit instalaci</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Pro umístění produktu vyberte stabilní, dobře větraný a bezprašný prostor mimo dosah přímého slunečního světla.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Odstraňte oranžovou přepravní pásku a ochranný plastový kryt.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Otevřete dvířka tiskové kazety. Odeberte pěnový blok, tiskovou kazetu, list zjišťování a přiloženou oranžovou přepravní pojistku. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Recyklujte pěnový blok, list zjišťování a přepravní pojistku.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Z konce tiskové kazety odstraňte oranžovou přepravní pojistku. Otáčením tiskové kazety nahoru a dolů zajistíte rovnoměrné rozvrstvení toneru. Zatáhnutím za chlopeň odstraňte pásku toneru. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Recyklujte přepravní pojistku a pásku toneru.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Vložte kazetu s tonerem do produktu a poté zavřete dvířka tiskové kazety.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Nastavte vodítka papíru a vložte papír lícem nahoru do zásobníku 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Připojte napájecí kabel. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Poznamenejte si číslo modelu, číslo produktu a sériové číslo pro registraci produktu.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Zapněte produkt.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Zahajte instalaci softwaru a postupujte podle pokynů na obrazovce.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Informace o instalaci bezdrátového modelu naleznete v <b>příručce Začínáme</b> v části <em>Bezdrátová instalace v systému Windows</em>, nebo v <b>uživatelské příručce</b> v části <em>Instalace produktu v bezdrátové síti</em>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Podle ilustrace nainstalujte výstupní přihrádku.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Nainstalujte protiprachový kryt.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Připojte k zařízení síťový kabel. Zkontrolujte, zda u síťového portu na zadní straně zařízení svítí jeden ze síťových indikátorů.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Vyčkejte asi čtyři minuty, než síť přiřadí produktu IP adresu, a poté z ovládacího panelu produktu vytiskněte konfigurační stránku. Chcete-li vytisknout stránku, stiskněte a podržte tlačítko <b>Spustit</b>. Jakmile začne blikat indikátor Připraveno, tlačítko uvolněte. V části <em>Informace o síti</em> vyhledejte IP adresu.</p></string8b></csww><daww><home1 type="content"><title>Animeret introduktionsvejledning</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Denne animerede introduktionsvejledning viser, hvordan du installerer og opsætter dit nye HP LaserJet-produkt.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Vælg produkt nedenfor</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-printerserien</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installation</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Trådløs installation</mainButt></prod1bButt> <series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560- og P1600-printerserien</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installation</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Netværksinstallation</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Hjem</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Installer printersoftware</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Se brugervejledningen</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien, USB-installation</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien, trådløs installation</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560-/P1600-serien, USB.installation</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560-/P1600-serien, netværksinstallation</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Begynd opsætningen</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Placer produktet i et stabilt, godt udluftet, støvfrit område uden direkte sollys.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Fjern al orange emballeringstape og plastikbeskyttelsen.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Åbn dækslet til printerpatronen. Fjern skumblokken, printerpatronen, registreringsarket og den medfølgende orange forsegling. <b>BEMÆRK!:</b> Genbrug skumblokken, registreringsarket og forseglingen.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Fjern den orange forsegling fra enden af printerpatronen. Drej printerpatronen frem og tilbage for at fordele toneren jævnt. Træk i tappen for at fjerne tonertapen. <b>BEMÆRK!:</b> Genbrug forseglingen og tonertapen.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Installer tonerpatronen i produktet, og luk dækslet til printerpatronen.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Juster papirstyrene, og ilæg papir i bakke 1 med forsiden nedad.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Tilslut netledningen. <b>BEMÆRK!:</b> Noter modelnummer, produktnummer og serienummer med henblik på produktregistrering.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Tænd for produktet.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Start softwareinstallationen, og følg instruktionerne på skærmen.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Hvis du vil installere en trådløs model, skal du se afsnittet <em>Windows trådløs installation</em> i <b>Introduktionsvejledningen</b>, eller afsnittet <em>Installer produktet på et trådløst netværk</em> i <b>Brugervejledningen</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Installer udskriftsbakken som vist her.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Installer støvdækslet.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Slut netværkskablet til produktet. Kontroller, at en af netværksindikatorerne på netværksporten bag på produktet lyser.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Vent ca. fire minutter, mens netværket tildeler en IP-adresse til produktet, og udskriv derefter en konfigurationsside fra produktets kontrolpanel. Hvis du vil udskrive siden, skal du trykke på knappen <b>Kør</b> og holde den nede, og slippe knappen, når klar-indikatoren begynder at lyse. Find IP-adressen i afsnittet <em>Netværksoplysninger</em>.</p></string8b></daww><deww><home1 type="content"><title>Animierter Leitfaden zur Inbetriebnahme</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>In diesem animierten Leitfaden zur Inbetriebnahme sehen Sie, wie Sie Ihr neues HP LaserJet-Produkt installieren und einrichten.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Wählen Sie unten Ihr Produkt aus.</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-Installation</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Drahtlos-Installation</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 und P1600 Printer Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-Installation</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Netzwerk-Installation</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Startseite</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Drucker-Software installieren</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Benutzerhandbuch anzeigen</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series – USB-Installation</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series – Drahtlos-Installation</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series – USB-Installation</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series – Netzwerk-Installation</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Setup starten</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Stellen Sie das Gerät an einem stabilen, gut durchlüfteten und staubfreien Ort auf, der direktem Sonnenlicht nicht ausgesetzt ist.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Entfernen Sie alle orangefarbenen Klebestreifen und das Schutzplastik.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Öffnen Sie die Druckpatronenklappe. Entfernen Sie den Schaumstoff, die Druckpatrone, das Suchblatt und die orangefarbene Transportsicherung. <b>HINWEIS:</b> Recyceln Sie den Schaumstoff, das Suchblatt und die Transportsicherung.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Entfernen Sie die orangefarbene Transportsicherung vom Ende der Druckpatrone. Bewegen Sie die Druckpatrone vorwärts und rückwärts, um den Toner gleichmäßig zu verteilen. Ziehen Sie an der Lasche, um das Klebeband zu entfernen. <b>HINWEIS:</b> Recyceln Sie die Transportsicherung und das Klebeband vom Toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Setzen Sie die Druckpatrone in den Drucker ein, und schließen Sie die Druckpatronenklappe.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Passen Sie die Papierführungen an, und legen Sie Papier mit der Vorderseite nach oben in Fach 1 ein.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Stecken Sie das Netzkabel ein. <b>HINWEIS:</b> Notieren Sie sich die Modellnummer, die Produktnummer und die Seriennummer für die Produktregistrierung.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Schalten Sie das Gerät ein.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Starten Sie die Softwareinstallation, und befolgen Sie die Anweisungen auf dem Bildschirm.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Um ein drahtloses Modell zu installieren, lesen Sie den Abschnitt <em>Windows – Kabellose Installation</em> im <b>Leitfaden zur Inbetriebnahme</b>, oder lesen Sie den Abschnitt <em>Installieren des Produkts in einem drahtlosen Netzwerk</em> im <b>Benutzerhandbuch</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Setzen Sie das Ausgabefach wie in der Abbildung dargestellt ein.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Bringen Sie den Staubschutzdeckel an.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Schließen Sie das Netzwerkkabel an das Gerät an. Vergewissern Sie sich, dass eine der Netzwerk-LEDs am Netzwerkanschluss auf der Rückseite des Geräts leuchtet.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Warten Sie ca. vier Minuten, bis das Netzwerk dem Gerät eine IP-Adresse zugeordnet hat, und drucken Sie dann eine Konfigurationsseite über das Bedienfeld des Geräts. Um die Seite zu drucken, halten Sie die <b>Start</b>-Taste gedrückt, und lassen Sie die Taste los, wenn die Bereit-LED zu blinken beginnt. Suchen Sie die IP-Adresse im Abschnitt <em>Netzwerkinformationen</em>.</p></string8b></deww><elww><home1 type="content"><title>Οδηγός έναρξης χρήσης με κινούμενες εικόνες</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Αυτός ο οδηγός έναρξης χρήσης με κινούμενες εικόνες σάς δείχνει πώς να εγκαταστήσετε και να ρυθμίσετε το νέο σας προϊόν HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Επιλέξτε το προϊόν σας</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Σειρά εκτυπωτών HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Εγκατάσταση μέσω USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Ασύρματη εγκατάσταση</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Σειρά εκτυπωτών HP LaserJet Pro P1560 και P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Εγκατάσταση μέσω USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Εγκατάσταση μέσω δικτύου</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Αρχική σελίδα</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Εγκατάσταση λογισμικού εκτυπωτή</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Προβολή οδηγού χρήσης</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Εγκατάσταση μέσω USB σειράς HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Ασύρματη εγκατάσταση σειράς HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Εγκατάσταση μέσω USB σειράς HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Εγκατάσταση μέσω δικτύου σειράς HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Έναρξη εγκατάστασης</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Τοποθετήστε το προϊόν σε ένα σταθερό σημείο, σε καλά αεριζόμενο χώρο χωρίς σκόνη και μακριά από το άμεσο ηλιακό φως.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Αφαιρέστε όλες τις πορτοκαλί ταινίες συσκευασίας και το προστατευτικό πλαστικό.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Ανοίξτε τη θύρα της κασέτας εκτύπωσης. Αφαιρέστε το προστατευτικό αφρολέξ, την κασέτα εκτύπωσης, το φύλλο περιγραφής και την προσαρτημένη πορτοκαλί ασφάλεια μεταφοράς. <b>ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ:</b> Ανακυκλώστε το προστατευτικό αφρολέξ, το φύλλο περιγραφής και την ασφάλεια μεταφοράς.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Αφαιρέστε την πορτοκαλί ασφάλεια μεταφοράς από το κάτω μέρος της κασέτας εκτύπωσης. Περιστρέψτε την κασέτα εκτύπωσης από εμπρός προς τα πίσω για ομοιόμορφη κατανομή του γραφίτη. Τραβήξτε τη γλωττίδα για να αφαιρέσετε την προστατευτική ταινία γραφίτη. <b>ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ:</b> Ανακυκλώστε την ασφάλεια μεταφοράς και την προστατευτική ταινία γραφίτη.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Τοποθετήστε την κασέτα γραφίτη στη συσκευή και κλείστε τη θύρα της κασέτας εκτύπωσης.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Προσαρμόστε τους οδηγούς χαρτιού και τοποθετήστε το χαρτί με την εμπρός όψη προς τα πάνω στο Δίσκο 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Συνδέστε το καλώδιο τροφοδοσίας. <b>ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ:</b> Καταγράψτε τον αριθμό μοντέλου, τον αριθμό προϊόντος και τον αριθμό σειράς για τη δήλωση προϊόντος.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Ενεργοποιήστε το προϊόν.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Εκκινήστε το λογισμικό εγκατάστασης και ακολουθήστε τις οδηγίες που εμφανίζονται στην οθόνη.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Για να εγκαταστήσετε μοντέλο με ασύρματη σύνδεση, ανατρέξτε στην ενότητα <em>Ασύρματη εγκατάσταση για Windows</em> στον <b>Οδηγό έναρξης χρήσης</b> ή ανατρέξτε στην ενότητα <em>Εγκατάσταση της συσκευής σε ασύρματο δίκτυο</em> του <b>Οδηγού χρήσης</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Εγκαταστήστε τη θήκη εξόδου όπως εμφανίζεται εδώ.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Εγκαταστήστε το προστατευτικό σκόνης.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Συνδέστε το καλώδιο δικτύου στο προϊόν. Βεβαιωθείτε ότι ανάβει μία από τις λυχνίες στη θύρα δικτύου που βρίσκεται στο πίσω μέρος της συσκευής.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Περιμένετε περίπου τέσσερα λεπτά έως ότου το δίκτυο να εκχωρήσει διεύθυνση IP για τη συσκευή και, στη συνέχεια, εκτυπώστε μια σελίδα διαμόρφωσης από τον πίνακα ελέγχου του προϊόντος. Για εκτύπωση της σελίδας, πατήστε παρατεταμένα το κουμπί <b>Μετάβαση</b> και, στη συνέχεια, αφήστε το όταν αρχίσει να αναβοσβήνει η λυχνία ετοιμότητας. Εντοπίστε τη διεύθυνση IP στην ενότητα <em>Πληροφορίες δικτύου</em>.</p></string8b></elww><esww><home1 type="content"><title>Guía de instalación inicial animada</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Esta guía de instalación inicial animada muestra cómo instalar y configurar el nuevo producto HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Seleccione su producto a continuación</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Impresora HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalación a través de USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalación inalámbrica</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Impr. HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560 y P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalación a través de USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalación a través de la red</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Inicio</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalar software de la impresora</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Ver la Guía del usuario</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instalación a través de USB de HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instalación inalámbrica de HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instalación a través de USB de HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instalación inalámbrica de HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Iniciar configuración</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Busque un lugar sólido, bien ventilado, sin polvo y alejado de la luz solar directa para colocar el producto.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Retire todo el plástico protector y el precinto naranja.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Abra la puerta de los cartuchos de impresión. Retire el bloque de espuma, el cartucho de impresión, la lámina y el bloqueo de transporte naranja. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicle el bloque de espuma, la lámina y el bloqueo de transporte.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Retire el bloqueo de transporte naranja del extremo del cartucho de impresión. Gire el cartucho de impresión de delante hacia atrás para distribuir el tóner uniformemente. Tire de la lengüeta para retirar el precinto del tóner. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicle el bloqueo de transporte y el precinto del tóner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Instale el cartucho de tóner en el producto y cierre la puerta del cartucho de impresión.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Ajuste las guías del papel y cargue el papel boca arriba en la bandeja 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Conecte el cable de alimentación. <b>NOTA:</b> Anote el número de modelo, número del producto y número de serie para registrar el producto.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Encienda el producto.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Inicie el software de instalación y siga las instrucciones que aparecen en pantalla.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Para instalar un modelo inalámbrico, consulte la sección <em>Instalación inalámbrica en Windows</em> de la <b>Guía de instalación inicial</b>, o consulte la sección <em>Instalación del producto en una red inalámbrica</em> de la <b>Guía del usuario</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Instale la bandeja de salida como se muestra aquí.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Instale la cubierta de protección contra el polvo.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Conecte el cable de red al producto. Compruebe que se enciende una de las luces de red en el puerto de red situado en la parte posterior del producto.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Espere unos cuatro minutos a que la red asigne una dirección IP al producto y, a continuación, imprima una página de configuración desde el panel de control del producto. Para imprimir la página, mantenga pulsado el botón <b>Continuar</b> y, a continuación, suelte el botón cuando la luz Preparada empiece a parpadear. Busque la dirección IP en la sección <em>Información de red</em>.</p></string8b></esww><etww><home1 type="content"><title>Animeeritud alustusjuhend</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>See animeeritud alustusjuhend näitab, kuidas uut HP LaserJeti printerit installida ja häälestada.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Valige allpool oma toode</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-seeria printerid</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB kaudu installimine</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Traadita võrgu kaudu installimine</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560- ja P1600-seeria printerid</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB kaudu installimine</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Võrgu kaudu installimine</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Avaleht</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Tarkvara installimine</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Vaadake kasutusjuhendit</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-seeria USB kaudu installimine</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-seeria traadita võrgu kaudu installimine</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-seeria USB kaudu installimine</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-seeria võrgu kaudu installimine</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Alustage häälestamist</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Valige toote paigutamiseks tugev pind hästi ventileeritud tolmuvabas alas, otsese päikesevalguse eest eemal.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Eemaldage tootelt oranž transporditeip ning kaitsev plastmaterjal.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Avage prindikasseti luuk. Eemaldage vahtmaterjal, prindikassett, tutvustusleht ning oranž transpordilukk. <b>MÄRKUS.</b> Andke vahtmaterjal, tutvustusleht ning transpordilukk ringlusse.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Eemaldage prindikasseti alumiselt osalt oranž transpordilukk. Pöörake prindikasseti esiosa tahapoole, et tooneri sisu jaotuks ühtlaselt. Toonerilt teibi eemaldamiseks tõmmake sakist. <b>MÄRKUS.</b> Andke transpordilukk ja tooneri teip ringlusse.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Asetage tooneri kassett tootesse oma kohale ja sulgege seejärel printerikasseti luuk.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Reguleerige paberijuhikuid ja asetage paber ülespidi esimesse salve.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Ühendage toitekaabel. <b>MÄRKUS.</b> Kirjutage mudeli number, toote number ja seerianumber toote registreerimiseks üles.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Lülitage printer sisse.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Alustage tarkvarainstalli ning järgige ekraanile ilmuvaid juhiseid.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Traadita mudeli installimiseks vaadake <b>Alustusjuhendi</b> jaotist <em>Juhtmevaba installimine Windowsis</em>, või <b>Kasutusjuhendi</b> jaotist <em>Toote installimine traadita võrgus</em>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Paigaldage väljastussalv vastavalt juhistele.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Paigaldage tolmukate.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Ühendage võrgukaabel tootega. Kontrollige, kas toote tagaküljel asuval võrgupordil süttib üks võrguühenduse olekutuledest.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Oodake umbes neli minutit, kuni tootele antakse võrgust IP-aadress ning printige seejärel toote juhtpaneeli kasutades konfigureerimisaruanne. Lehe printimiseks hoidke all nuppu <b>Mine</b> ning vabastage nupp, kui valmisolekutuli hakkab vilkuma. Otsige jaotisest <em>Network Information (Võrguteave)</em> IP-aadress.</p></string8b></etww><fiww><home1 type="content"><title>Animoitu aloitusopas</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Tämä animoitu aloitusopas avustaa HP LaserJet -tuotteen asentamisessa ja määrittämisessä.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Valitse tuote</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 -tulostinsarja</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-asennus</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Langaton asennus</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560- ja P1600-tulostinsarja</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-asennus</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Verkkoasennus</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Alkuun</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Asenna tulostinohjelmisto</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Katso Käyttöopasta</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sarjan USB-asennus</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sarjan langaton asennus</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 -sarjan USB-asennus</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 -sarjan verkkoasennus</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Aloita asennus</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Sijoita laite tukevalle alustalle pölyttömään paikkaan, johon aurinko ei paista suoraan ja jossa on hyvä ilmanvaihto.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Irrota kaikki oranssit pakkausteipit ja suojamuovi laitteesta.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Avaa tulostuskasetin luukku. Irrota solumuovipala, tulostuskasetti, tutustumisarkki ja kiinnitetty oranssi kuljetuslukko. <b>HUOMAUTUS:</b> Hävitä solumuovipala, tutustumisarkki ja kuljetuslukko.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Irrota oranssi kuljetuslukko tulostuskasetin päästä. Tasoita väriaine kääntelemällä tulostuskasettia edestakaisin. Poista väriaineen teippi vetämällä kielekkeestä. <b>HUOMAUTUS:</b> Hävitä kuljetuslukko ja väriaineen teippi.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Asenna värikasetti laitteeseen ja sulje tulostuskasetin luukku.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Säädä paperinohjaimet ja lisää paperia tulostuspuoli ylöspäin lokeroon 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Kytke virtajohto. <b>HUOMAUTUS:</b> Kirjoita muistiin malli-, tuote- ja sarjanumero tuoterekisteröintiä varten.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Kytke laitteeseen virta.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Käynnistä ohjelmiston asennus ja seuraa näytön ohjeita.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Langattoman mallin asennusohjeet ovat <em>aloitusoppaan</em> <b>Langaton Windows-asennus</b> -kohdassa ja <em>käyttöoppaan</em> <b>Laitteen asentaminen langattomaan verkkoon</b> -kohdassa.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Asenna tulostelokero tämän kuvan mukaisesti.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Asenna pölysuojus.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Liitä verkkokaapeli laitteeseen. Varmista, että jokin laitteen taustapuolen verkkoportin valoista palaa.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Odota noin neljä minuuttia, kunnes verkko määrittää laitteelle IP-osoitteen, ja tulosta asetussivu laitteen ohjauspaneelista. Tulosta painamalla <b>Siirry</b>-painiketta pitkään. Vapauta painike, kun valmiusvalo alkaa vilkkua. Etsi IP-osoite <em>Verkkotiedot</em>-kohdasta.</p></string8b></fiww><frww><home1 type="content"><title>Guide de mise en route animé</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Ce guide de mise en route animé vous explique comment installer et configurer votre nouveau produit HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Sélectionnez votre produit ci-dessous</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installation USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installation sans fil</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1560 et P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installation USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installation réseau</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Accueil</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Installer le logiciel de l'imprimante</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Voir le Guide de l’utilisateur</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Installation USB de l'imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Installation sans fil de l'imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Installation USB de l'imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Installation réseau de l'imprimante HP LaserJet Pro série P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Commencer la configuration</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Choisissez un support solide et un endroit propre, bien aéré et à l'abri du rayonnement direct du soleil pour placer votre produit.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Retirez la bande d'expédition orange et la protection en plastique.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Ouvrez la porte d'accès à la cartouche d'impression. Retirez la mousse, la cartouche d'impression, la fiche de présentation et le dispositif de sécurité d'expédition orange. <b>REMARQUE :</b> recyclez la mousse, la fiche de présentation et le dispositif de sécurité d'expédition.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Retirez le dispositif de sécurité d'expédition orange situé à l'extrémité de la cartouche d'impression. Secouez légèrement la cartouche d'impression d'avant en arrière pour répartir le toner de façon homogène. Tirez sur la languette pour retirer la bande de protection du toner. <b>REMARQUE :</b> recyclez le dispositif de sécurité d'expédition et la bande de protection du toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Insérez la cartouche d'impression dans le produit, puis refermez le panneau.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Réglez les guides-papier et chargez le papier côté recto vers le haut dans le bac 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Branchez le cordon d'alimentation. <b>REMARQUE :</b> notez le numéro de modèle, le numéro du produit et le numéro de série nécessaires à l'enregistrement du produit.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Mettez le produit sous tension.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Lancez l'installation du logiciel et suivez les instructions affichées à l'écran.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Pour installer un modèle sans fil, consultez la section <em>Installation sans fil sous Windows</em> du <b>Guide de mise en route</b> ou la section <em>Installation du produit sur un réseau sans fil</em> du <b>Guide de l'utilisateur</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Installez le réceptacle de sortie comme indiqué.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Installez le capot antipoussière.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Branchez le câble réseau à l'imprimante. Vérifiez qu'un des voyants réseau est allumé sur le port réseau situé à l'arrière du produit.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Patientez environ quatre minutes, le délai nécessaire au réseau pour qu'il attribue une adresse IP au produit, puis imprimez une page de configuration en utilisant le panneau de commande du produit. Pour imprimer la page, maintenez le bouton <b>Go</b> enfoncé, puis relâchez-le lorsque le voyant Prêt commence à clignoter. Notez l'adresse IP dans la section <em>Informations réseau</em>.</p></string8b></frww><heww><home1 type="content"><title>מדריך מונפש להפעלה ראשונה</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>.HP LaserJet מדריך מונפש זה להפעלה ראשונה מציג את אופן החיבור וההגדרה של מוצר</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>בחר את המוצר הרלוונטי</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>USB התקנת «</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>התקנה אלחוטית «</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 / P1600 Printer Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>USB התקנת «</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>התקנת רשת «</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>מסך ראשי «</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>התקן את תוכנת המדפסת «</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>עיין במדריך למשתמש «</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB התקנת - HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>התקנה אלחוטית - HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB התקנת - HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>התקנת רשת - HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>התחל בהתקנה «</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>.הצב את המוצר באזור יציב, מאוורר ונקי מאבק, הרחק מאור שמש ישיר</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>.הסר את כל סרטי המשלוח הכתומים ואת הפלסטיק המגן</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>.פתח את דלת מחסנית ההדפסה.ואת סגר האריזה הכתום Discovery -הוצא את הספוג הקשיח, את מחסנית ההדפסה, את גיליון ה.ואת סגר האריזה Discovery - מחזר את הספוג הקשיח, את גיליון ה <b>:הערה</b></p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>.הסר את סגר האריזה הכתום מקצה מחסנית ההדפסה. סובב את מחסנית האריזה מלפנים לאחור כדי לפזר את הטונר בצורה שווה.משוך את הלשונית כדי להסיר הסרט מהטונר.מחזר את סגר האריזה ואת הסרט של הטונר <b>:הערה</b> </p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>.התקן את מחסנית הטונר במוצר וסגור את דלת מחסנית ההדפסה</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>.כוונן את מכווני הנייר וטען את הנייר כלפי מעלה במגש 1</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>.חבר את כבל המתח.רשום את מספר הדגם, את מספר המוצר ואת המספר הסידורי לצורך רישום המוצר <b>:הערה</b></p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>.הפעל את המוצר</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>.התחל בהתקנת התוכנה ופעל בהתאם להוראות שיופיעו במסך</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless> ,<b>במדריך להפעלה ראשונה</b> <em>Windows-התקנה אלחוטית ב</em> להתקנת דגם אלחוטי, עיין בסעיף                                     .<b>במדריך למשתמש</b> <em>התקן את המוצר ברשת אלחוטית</em> או עיין בסעיף</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>.התקן את סל הפלט כמוצג כאן</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>.התקן את הכיסוי למניעת אבק</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>.ודא שאחת מנוריות הרשת ביציאת הרשת הממוקמת בגב המוצר דולקת .חבר את כבל הרשת למוצר</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>.למוצר ואז הדפס דף תצורה מלוח הבקרה של המוצר IP המתן כארבע דקות עד שהרשת תקצה כתובת.ושחרר אותו כאשר הנורית 'מוכן' תתחיל להבהב <b>בצע</b> להדפסת העמוד, לחץ לחיצה ארוכה על הלחצן.(מידע על הרשת) <em>Network Information</em> במקטע IP-אתר את כתובת ה</p></string8b></heww><hrww><home1 type="content"><title>Animirani vodič za početak rada</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Ovaj animirani vodič za početak rada prikazuje kako instalirati i postaviti novi HP LaserJet uređaj.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Odaberite svoj uređaj u nastavku</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Serija pisača HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB instalacija</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Bežična instalacija</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Serija pisača HP LaserJet Pro P1560 i P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB instalacija</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Mrežna instalacija</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Početak</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalacija softvera za pisač</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Pregled korisničkog vodiča</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB instalacija pisača serije HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Bežična instalacija pisača serije HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB instalacija pisača serije HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Mrežna instalacija pisača serije HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>»Početak postavljanja</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Proizvod postavite na čvrstu površinu do koje ne dopire izravno sunčevo svjetlo u dobro prozračenom prostoru bez prašine.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Uklonite sve narančaste plastične dijelove za transport i zaštitu.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Otvorite vrata spremnika za ispis. Izvadite blok pjene, spremnik za ispis, list s podacima i pričvršćeni narančasti transportni zatvarač. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Reciklirajte blok pjene, list s podacima i transportni zatvarač.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Skinite narančasti transportni zatvarač na kraju spremnika za ispis. Okrećite spremnik za ispis s prednje na stražnju stranu kako bi se toner jednoliko rasporedio. Povucite jezičak kako biste uklonili traku tonera. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Reciklirajte transportni zatvarač i traku tonera.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Umetnite spremnik s tonerom u proizvod i potom zatvorite vratašca spremnika za ispis.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Podesite vodilice za papir i umetnite papir u ladicu 1 licem okrenutim prema gore.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Priključite kabel za napajanje. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Zabilježite broj modela, broj proizvoda i serijski broj radi registracije proizvoda.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Uključite proizvod.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Pokrenite instalaciju softvera i slijedite upute na zaslonu.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Za instalaciju bežičnog modela pogledajte odjeljak <em>Bežična instalacija za Windows</em> u <b>Vodiču za početak rada</b> ili odjeljak <em>Instaliranje uređaja na kabelskoj mreži</em> u <b>Korisničkom priručniku</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Postavite izlaznu ladicu kako je prikazano ovdje.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Postavite poklopac za zaštitu od prašine.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Mrežni kabel priključite na uređaj. Provjerite svijetli li neki od mrežnih indikatora na mrežnom priključku koji je smješten na stražnjoj strani uređaja.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Pričekajte oko četiri minute da mreža proizvodu dodijeli IP adresu, a zatim ispišite stranicu konfiguracije pomoću upravljačke ploče proizvoda. Za ispis stranice pritisnite i držite gumb <b>Go</b> (Kreni), a potom ga, kad indikator spremnosti počne treperiti, otpustite. IP adresu možete pronaći u odjeljku <em>Informacije o mreži</em>.</p></string8b></hrww><huww><home1 type="content"><title>Animált bemutató az alapvető tudnivalókról</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Ez alapvető tudnivalókról szóló animált bemutató ismerteti az új HP LaserJet készülék üzembe helyezésének és beállításának módját.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Válassza ki saját készülékét alább</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 nyomtatósorozat</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB telepítés</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Vezeték nélküli telepítés</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 és P1600 nyomtatósorozat</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB telepítés</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Hálózati telepítés</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Főoldal</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» A nyomtatószoftver telepítése</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» A Felhasználói kézikönyv megtekintése</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sorozat USB telepítés</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sorozat vezeték nélküli telepítés</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 sorozat USB telepítés</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 sorozat hálózati telepítés</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Az üzembe helyezés megkezdése</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>A készüléket szilárd, jól szellőző, pormentes helyen állítsa fel, és ne tegye ki közvetlen napfény hatásának.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Távolítsa el az összes narancssárga szállítási szalagot és műanyag védőtasakot.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Nyissa ki a nyomtatókazetta-tartó fedelét. Vegye ki a habszivacstömböt, a nyomtatókazettát, az útmutatólapot és a narancssárga szállítókapcsot. <b>MEGJEGYZÉS:</b> Hasznosítsa újra a habszivacstömböt, az útmutatólapot és a szállítókapcsot.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Távolítsa el a narancssárga szállítókapcsot a nyomtatókazetta végéről. A nyomtatókazetta forgatásával oszlassa el a festéket egyenletesen. A fül húzásával távolítsa el a szalagot a kazettáról. <b>MEGJEGYZÉS:</b> Hasznosítsa újra a szállítókapcsot és a szalagot.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Tegye be a nyomtatókazettát a készülékbe, és ezután csukja be a nyomtatókazetta-tartó fedelét.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Igazítsa be a papírvezetőket, és töltse be a papírt az 1. tálcába nyomtatandó oldalával felfelé.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Csatlakoztassa a tápkábelt. <b>MEGJEGYZÉS:</b> Jegyezze fel a típusszámot, termékszámot és sorozatszámot a termékregisztrációhoz.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Kapcsolja be a készüléket.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Indítsa el a szoftvertelepítést, és kövesse a képernyőn megjelenő utasításokat.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Vezeték nélküli készülék telepítéséhez olvassa el a <em>Windows vezeték nélküli telepítés</em> részt az <b>Alapvető tudnivalók kézikönyvében</b>, vagy olvassa el <em>A készülék telepítése vezeték nélküli hálózatra</em> részt a <b>Felhasználói kézikönyvben</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Helyezze fel a kimeneti tálcát az itt látható módon.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Helyezze fel a porvédőt.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Csatlakoztassa a hálózati kábelt a készülékhez. Ellenőrizze, hogy világít-e a készülék hátsó részén található hálózati port két jelzőfényének egyike.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Várjon kb. négy percet, hogy a hálózat hozzárendeljen egy IP-címet a készülékhez, majd a készülék kezelőpaneljéről nyomtasson ki egy konfigurációs oldalt. Az oldal kinyomtatásához tartsa lenyomva az <b>Indítás</b> gombot, majd engedje el a gombot, amikor az üzemkész jelzőfény villogni kezd. Keresse meg az IP-címet a <em>Hálózati információk</em> részben.</p></string8b></huww><idww><home1 type="content"><title>Panduan Persiapan Dengan Animasi</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Panduan persiapan yang dilengkapi animasi ini memperlihatkan cara menginstal dan menyiapkan produk HP LaserJet baru.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Pilih produk Anda di bawah ini</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Seri Printer HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalasi USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalasi Nirkabel</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Seri Printer HP LaserJet Pro P1560 dan P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalasi USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalasi Jaringan</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Halaman awal</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instal Perangkat Lunak Printer</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Lihat Panduan Pengguna</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instalasi USB HP LaserJet Pro Seri P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instalasi Nirkabel HP LaserJet Pro Seri P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instalasi USB HP LaserJet Pro Seri P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instalasi nirkabel HP LaserJet Pro Seri P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Mulai Pengaturan</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Untuk meletakkan produk, pilih tempat yang kokoh, berventilasi baik, bebas debu, dan jauh dari sinar matahari langsung.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Lepaskan semua pita oranye dan plastik pelindung.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Buka pintu kartrid cetak. Lepaskan blok gabus, kartrid cetak, lembar petunjuk, dan segel pengaman oranye yang terpasang. <b>CATATAN:</b> Daur ulang blok gabus, lembar petunjuk, dan segel pengaman.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Lepas segel pengaman oranye dari ujung kartrid cetak. Putar kartrid cetak dari depan ke belakang untuk meratakan toner. Tarik tab untuk melepas pita toner. <b>CATATAN:</b> Daur ulang segel pengaman dan pita toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Pasang kartrid toner pada produk dan tutup pintu kartrid cetak.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Atur pemandu kertas dan muat kertas menghadap ke atas pada Baki 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Colokkan kabel listrik. <b>CATATAN:</b> Catat nomor model, nomor produk, dan nomor seri untuk pendaftaran produk.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Hidupkan produk.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Mulai instalasi perangkat lunak dan ikuti petunjuk pada layar.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Untuk menginstal model nirkabel, baca bagian <em>Instalasi Nirkabel Windows</em> pada <b>Panduan Persiapan</b>, atau baca bagian <em>Menginstal produk di jaringan nirkabel</em> pada <b>Panduan Pengguna</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Pasang nampan keluaran seperti diperlihatkan di sini.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Pasang pelindung debu.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Sambungkan kabel jaringan ke produk. Pastikan salah satu lampu jaringan menyala pada port jaringan yang terdapat di bagian belakang produk.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Tunggu sekitar empat menit sampai jaringan menetapkan sebuah alamat IP untuk produk, lalu cetak halaman konfigurasi dari panel kontrol produk. Untuk mencetak halaman, tekan dan tahan tombol <b>Go</b>, lalu lepaskan tombol bila lampu siap mulai berkedip. Tentukan alamat IP di bagian <em>Informasi Jaringan</em>.</p></string8b></idww><itww><home1 type="content"><title>Guida rapida animata</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Questa guida rapida animata illustra come installare e configurare il nuovo prodotto HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Selezionare il prodotto di seguito</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Stampante HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installazione USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installazione wireless</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Stampante HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560 e P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installazione USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installazione di rete</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Pagina iniziale</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Installa software stampante</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Visualizzazione del manuale dell'utente</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Installazione USB unità HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Installazione wireless unità HP LaserJet Pro serie P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Installazione USB unità HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Installazione di rete unità HP LaserJet Pro serie P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Inizio della configurazione</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Posizionare il prodotto in un'area piana, ben ventilata, priva di polvere e lontana dalla luce diretta dei raggi solari.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Rimuovere tutto il nastro da trasporto arancione e la plastica protettiva.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Aprire lo sportello della cartuccia di stampa. Rimuovere il blocco in spugna, la cartuccia di stampa, il foglio di rilevamento e il fermo di trasporto arancione attaccato. <b>NOTA:</b> è possibile riciclare il blocco in spugna, il foglio di rilevamento e il fermo di trasporto.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Rimuovere il fermo di trasporto arancione dall'estremità della cartuccia di stampa. Ruotare la cartuccia di stampa avanti e indietro per distribuire in modo uniforme il toner. Tirare la linguetta per rimuovere il nastro del toner. <b>NOTA:</b> è possibile riciclare il fermo di trasporto e il nastro del toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Inserire la cartuccia del toner nel prodotto e chiudere lo sportello della cartuccia di stampa.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Regolare le guide della carta e caricare la carta nel vassoio 1 con il lato di stampa rivolto verso l'alto.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Collegare il cavo di alimentazione. <b>NOTA:</b> prendere nota del numero di modello, del numero di prodotto e del numero di serie per la registrazione del prodotto.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Accendere il prodotto.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Avviare l'installazione del software e seguire le istruzioni riportate sullo schermo.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Per installare un modello wireless, fare riferimento alla sezione relativa all'<em>installazione wireless in Windows</em> della <b>Guida introduttiva</b> oppure alla sezione relativa all'<em>installazione del prodotto in una rete wireless</em> della <b>Guida per l'utente</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Installare lo scomparto di uscita come illustrato di seguito.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Installare il coperchio antipolvere.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Collegare il cavo di rete al prodotto. Verificare che sia accesa una delle spie di rete della porta di rete sul retro del prodotto.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Attendere circa quattro minuti affinché la rete assegni un indirizzo IP al prodotto e stampare la pagina di configurazione dal pannello di controllo del prodotto. Per stampare la pagina, tenere premuto il pulsante <b>Go</b>, quindi rilasciarlo quando la spia Pronta inizia a lampeggiare. Individuare l'indirizzo IP nella sezione sulle <em>informazioni di rete</em>.</p></string8b></itww><kkww><home1 type="content"><title>Жұмысқа дайындық жөніндегі анимациялық нұсқаулық</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Осы жұмысқа дайындық жөніндегі анимациялық нұсқаулықта жаңа HP LaserJet принтерін орнату және оның параметрлерін орнату тәсілдері көрсетіледі.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Төменнен өнімді таңдаңыз</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 принтер сериясы</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB арқылы пайдалану үшін орнату</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Сымсыз пайдалану үшін орнату</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560, P1600 сериялары</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB арқылы пайдалану үшін орнату</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Желіде пайдалану үшін орнату</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Негізгі бет</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Принтердің бағдарламалық құралын орнату</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Пайдаланушы нұсқаулығын көру</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 MFP сериясы, USB арқылы орнату</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 MFP сериясы, сымсыз байланыс арқылы орнату</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 MFP сериясы, USB арқылы орнату</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 MFP сериясы, желі арқылы орнату</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Орнатуды бастаңыз</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Өнімді орналастыру үшін берік, жақсы желдетілетін, шаңсыз, күн сәулесі тікелей түспейтін жерді таңдаңыз.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Барлық қызғылт сары таспаларды және пластик қорғағыштарды алып тастаңыз.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Баспа картриджінің есігін ашыңыз. Поролонды, баспа картриджін, ақпарат парағын және тағылған қызғылт сары тасымалдау бекітпесін алып тастаңыз. <b>ЕСКЕРТПЕ</b> Поролонды, ақпарат парағын және тасымалдау бекітпесін қайта өңдеуге өткізіңіз.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Баспа картриджінің ұшындағы қызғылт сары тасымалдау бекітпесін алып тастаңыз. Тонердің біркелкі жайылуы үшін, баспа картриджін алға-артқа шайқаңыз. Тонер таспасын алып тастау үшін, тілін тартыңыз. <b>ЕСКЕРТПЕ</b> Тасымалдау бекітпесі мен тонер таспасын қайта өңдеуге өткізіңіз.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Баспа картриджін өнімге салып, баспа картриджінің қақпағын жабыңыз.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Қағаз бағыттағыштарын реттеңіз де, қағаз бетін жоғары қаратып, 1-науаға салыңыз.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Қуат сымын розеткаға қосыңыз. <b>ЕСКЕРТПЕ</b> Өнімді тіркеу үшін, үлгі, өнім және сериялық нөмірлерді жазып алыңыз.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Өнімді қосыңыз.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Бағдарламалық құралды орнатып, экрандағы нұсқауларды орындаңыз.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Сымсыз үлгіні орнату үшін, <b>Жұмысқа дайындық жөніндегі нұсқаулық</b> ішіндегі <em>Windows жүйесінде сымсыз орнату</em> бөлімін қараңыз немесе <b>Пайдаланушы нұсқаулығы</b> ішіндегі <em>Құрылғыны сымсыз желіде орнату</em> бөлімін қараңыз.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Шығару науасын осы жерде көрсетілгендей орнатыңыз.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Шаңнан қорғау қақпағын орнатыңыз.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Желілік кабельді өнімге қосыңыз. Өнімнің артында орналасқан желілік порт шамдарының біреуінің жанып тұрғанын тексеріңіз.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Желінің өнімге IP мекенжайын тағайындауын төрт минуттай күтіңіз, одан кейін өнімнің басқару тақтасынан конфигурациялық бетті басып шығарыңыз. Бетті басып шығару үшін, <b>Go</b> (Орындау) түймесін басып тұрыңыз да, дайындық шамы жыпылықтай бастағанда, түймені босатыңыз. IP мекенжайын <em>Network Information</em> (Желі ақпараты) бөлімінен табыңыз.</p></string8b></kkww><koww><home1 type="content"><title>동영상 시작 설명서</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>이 동영상 시작 설명서는 새로운 HP LaserJet 제품의 설치 및 설정 방법을 보여줍니다.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>아래에서 제품을 선택하십시오.</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 프린터 시리즈</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 설치</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 무선 설치</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 프린터 시리즈</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 설치</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 네트워크 설치</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» 홈</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» 프린터 소프트웨어 설치</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» 사용 설명서 보기</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 USB 설치</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 시리즈 무선 설치</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 시리즈 USB 설치</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 시리즈 네트워크 설치</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» 설치 시작</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>직사광선을 피하여 바닥이 단단하고 환기가 잘 되며 먼지가 없는 장소를 선택하여 제품을 내려 놓습니다.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>주황색 테이프 및 보호 비닐을 모두 떼어냅니다.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>토너 카트리지 도어를 엽니다. 완충재, 토너 카트리지, 제품 안내서 및 부착된 주황색 포장 잠금 장치를 제거합니다. <b>참고:</b> 완충재, 제품 안내서 및 포장 잠금 장치는 재활용하십시오.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>토너 카트리지 끝에서 주황색 포장 잠금 장치를 제거합니다. 토너 카트리지를 앞뒤로 돌리듯이 움직여 토너를 고르게 분산시킵니다. 탭을 당겨 토너 테이프를 떼어냅니다. <b>참고:</b> 포장 잠금 장치와 토너 테이프는 재활용하십시오.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>토너 카트리지를 제품에 설치하고 토너 카트리지 덮개를 닫습니다.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>용지 조정대를 맞추고 인쇄면이 위를 향하도록 용지함 1에 넣습니다.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>전원 코드를 연결합니다. <b>참고:</b> 제품 등록을 위해 모델 번호, 제품 번호 및 일련 번호를 기록해 둡니다.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>제품을 켭니다.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>소프트웨어 설치를 시작하고 화면의 지시에 따릅니다.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>무선 모델을 설치하려면 <b>시작 설명서</b>에서 <em>Windows 무선 설치</em> 섹션을 참조하거나 <b>사용 설명서</b>의 <em>무선 네트워크에 제품 설치</em> 섹션을 참조하십시오.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>여기에 나온 대로 출력 용지함을 설치합니다.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>먼지 덮개를 설치합니다.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>네트워크 케이블을 제품에 연결합니다. 제품 뒷면의 네트워크 포트에 네트워크 표시등 중 하나가 켜졌는지 확인합니다.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>네트워크가 제품에 IP 주소를 할당할 때까지 약 5분간 기다린 후, 제품 제어판에서 구성 페이지를 인쇄합니다. 해당 페이지를 인쇄하려면 준비등이 깜박거릴 때까지 <b>이동</b> 단추를 길게 누릅니다.<em>네트워크 정보</em> 섹션에서 IP 주소를 확인합니다.</p></string8b></koww><ltww><home1 type="content"><title>Animuotas darbo pradžios vadovas</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Šis animuotas darbo pradžios vadovas parodo, kaip įdiegti ir nustatyti jūsų naują „HP LaserJet“ gaminį.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Žemiau pasirinkite savo gaminį</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1100 MFP“ spausdintuvo serija</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB diegimas</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Belaidžio ryšio diegimas</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1560“ ir P1600 spausdintuvų serija</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB diegimas</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Tinklo diegimas</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Pagrindinis puslapis</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Diegti spausdintuvo programinę įrangą</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Peržiūrėti vartotojo vadovą</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1100“ serijos USB diegimas</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1100 MFP“ serijos belaidžių modelių diegimas</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600“ serijos USB diegimas</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>„HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600“ serijos tinklo diegimas</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Pradėti sąranką</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Gaminiui padėti pasirinkite tvirtą pagrindą gerai ventiliuojamoje nedulkėtoje vietoje, kuri būtų atokiau nuo tiesioginių saulės spindulių.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Nuo gaminio pašalinkite visą oranžinės spalvos pakavimo juostelę ir apsauginį plastiko sluoksnį.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Atidarykite spausdinimo kasetės dureles. Išimkite apsaugines putas, spausdinimo kasetę, aprašymą ir pritvirtintą, oranžinę transportavimo apsaugą. <b>PASTABA:</b> Perdirbkite apsaugines putas, aprašymą ir transportavimo apsaugą.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Nuimkite oranžinę transportavimo apsaugą nuo spausdinimo kasetės dugno. Pavartykite spausdinimo kasetę, kad lygiai pasiskirstytų dažai. Norėdami ištraukti prie dažų kasetės pritvirtintą juostelę, patraukite fiksatorių. <b>PASTABA:</b> Perdirbkite transportavimo apsaugą ir prie dažų kasetės pritvirtintą juostelę.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Įmontuokite dažų kasetę į gaminį ir uždarykite spausdinimo kasetės dureles.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Pakoreguokite popieriaus kreiptuvus ir įdėkite popierių spausdinimo puse į viršų į 1 dėklą.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Prijunkite maitinimo laidą. <b>PASTABA:</b> Registruodami produktą įrašykite modelio numerį, produkto numerį ir serijos numerį.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Įjunkite gaminį.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Pradėkite programinės įrangos diegimą ir vadovaukitės ekrane pateiktomis instrukcijomis.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Norėdami įdiegti belaidį modelį, perskaitykite dalį <em>„Windows“ belaidžio ryšio diegimas</em>, esančią <b>Darbo pradžios vadove</b> arba – dalį <em>Gaminio diegimas belaidžiame tinkle</em>, esančią <b>Vartotojo vadove</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Įmontuokite išvesties dėklą taip, kaip parodyta čia.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Įmontuokite apsaugą nuo dulkių.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Prie produkto prijunkite tinklo kabelį. Patikrinkite, ar dega viena iš tinklo lempučių, esančių gaminio tinklo prievado galinėje pusėje.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Palaukite apie 4 minutes, kol tinklas priskirs produktui IP adresą, tada išspausdinkite konfigūracijos puslapį iš gaminio valdymo pulto. Norėdami išspausdinti puslapį, spustelėkite ir palaikykite nuspaudę mygtuką <b>Go</b> (vykdyti). Jį atleiskite, kai parengties lemputė pradės mirksėti. Raskite IP adresą skyriuje <em>Tinklo informacija</em>.</p></string8b></ltww><lvww><home1 type="content"><title>Darba sākšanas pamācība ar attēliem</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Šajā darba sākšanas pamācībā ar attēliem ir parādīts, kā uzstādīt un iestatīt HP LaserJet iekārtu.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Zemāk atlasiet savu iekārtu</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sērija</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalēšana, izmantojot USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalēšana bezvadu tīklā</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 un P1600 sērija</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalēšana, izmantojot USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalēšana tīklā</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Sākums</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Printera programmatūras instalēšana</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Lietotāja rokasgrāmata</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sērijas iekārtu instalēšana, izmantojot USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 sērijas iekārtu instalēšana bezvadu tīklā</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 sērijas iekārtu instalēšana, izmantojot USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 sērijas iekārtu instalēšana tīklā</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Sākt uzstādīšanu</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Novietojiet iekārtu stabilā, labi ventilētā vietā, kur nav putekļu un tiešu saules staru.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Noņemiet visu oranžo transportēšanas lenti un plastmasas iepakojumu.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Atveriet drukas kasetnes vāku. Izņemiet putuplasta elementu, drukas kasetni, apraksta lapu un ievietoto oranžo transportēšanas fiksatoru. <b>PIEZĪME.</b> Nododiet putuplasta elementu, apraksta lapu un transportēšanas fiksatoru otrreizējai pārstrādei.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Noņemiet oranžo transportēšanas fiksatoru no drukas kasetnes apakšas. Pagroziet drukas kasetni uz priekšu un atpakaļ, lai vienmērīgi sadalītu toneri. Pavelciet cilpiņu, lai izņemtu tonera lenti. <b>PIEZĪME.</b> Nododiet transportēšanas fiksatoru un tonera lenti otrreizējai pārstrādei.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Ielieciet drukas kasetni iekārtā un aizveriet drukas kasetnes vāku.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Noregulējiet papīra vadotnes un ielieciet papīru 1. padevē ar apdrukājamo pusi uz augšu.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Pievienojiet barošanas vadu.<b>PIEZĪME.</b> Pierakstiet modeļa numuru, iekārtas numuru un sērijas numuru, lai varētu reģistrēt iekārtu.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Ieslēdziet iekārtu.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Sāciet programmatūras instalēšanu un izpildiet ekrānā redzamās instrukcijas.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Informāciju par bezvadu iekārtas instalēšanu skatiet <b>Darba sākšanas pamācības</b> sadaļā <em>Windows instalēšana bezvadu tīklā</em> vai <b>Lietotāja rokasgrāmatas</b> sadaļā <em>Iekārtas instalēšana bezvadu tīklā</em>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Uzstādiet izdruku uztvērēju, kā parādīts šeit.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Uzstādiet putekļu aizsargu.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Savienojiet tīkla kabeli ar iekārtu. Pārbaudiet, vai iekārtas aizmugurē iedegas kāds no tīkla portā esošajiem indikatoriem.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Gaidiet aptuveni četras minūtes, kamēr tīkls piešķir iekārtai IP adresi, un pēc tam, izmantojot iekārtas vadības paneli, izdrukājiet konfigurācijas lapu. Lai izdrukātu lapu, nospiediet un turiet pogu <b>Go</b> (Aiziet!). Atlaidiet pogu, kad sāk mirgot gatavības indikators. Sadaļā <em>Network Information</em> (Tīkla informācija) atrodiet IP adresi.</p></string8b></lvww><nlww><home1 type="content"><title>Geanimeerde beknopte installatiehandleiding</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Deze geanimeerde beknopte installatiehandleiding laat u zien hoe u uw nieuwe HP LaserJet-product installeert en instelt.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Selecteer uw product hieronder</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 printerserie</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installatie</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Draadloze installatie</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 en P1600 printerseries</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installatie</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Netwerkinstallatie</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Home</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Printersoftware installeren</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Gebruikershandleiding weergeven</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB-installatie HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serie</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Draadloze installatie HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serie</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB-installatie HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serie</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Netwerkinstallatie HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serie</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Installatie starten</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Plaats het apparaat op een stevige, goed geventileerde, stofvrije plek uit direct zonlicht.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Verwijder de oranje transporttape en beschermplastic van het apparaat.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Open de klep van de printcartridge. Verwijder het schuimblok, de printcartridge, het detectievel en de oranje transportvergrendeling. <b>OPMERKING:</b> Recycle het schuimblok, het detectievel en de transportvergrendeling.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Verwijder de oranje transportvergrendeling van de printcartridge. Draai de printcartridge van voor naar achter om de toner gelijkmatig te verdelen. Trek aan het lipje om de tonertape te verwijderen. <b>OPMERKING:</b> Recycle de transportvergrendeling en tonertape.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Plaats de tonercartridge in het product en sluit de printcartridgeklep.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Stel de papiergeleiders in en plaats papier met de te bedrukken zijde omhoog in lade 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Sluit het netsnoer aan. <b>OPMERKING:</b> Noteer het modelnummer, productnummer en serienummer voor de productregistratie.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Schakel het apparaat in.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Start de software-installatie en volg de instructies op het scherm.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Als u een draadloos model wilt installeren, raadpleegt u het gedeelte <em>Draadloze installatie in Windows</em> in de <b>Beknopte installatiehandleiding</b> of het gedeelte <em>Het product verbinden met een draadloos netwerk</em> in de <b>Gebruikershandleiding</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Plaats de uitvoerbak zoals hier getoond.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Plaats de stofkap.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Sluit de netwerkkabel op het product aan. Controleer of een van de netwerklampjes op de netwerkpoort aan de achterzijde van het apparaat brandt.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Wacht ongeveer vier minuten tot het netwerk een IP-adres aan het product heeft toegekend en druk een configuratiepagina af vanaf het bedieningspaneel van het product. Voor het afdrukken van de pagina houdt u de knop <b>Start</b> ingedrukt en laat u de knop los zodra de Gereed-lampjes beginnen te knipperen. Zoek het IP-adres in het gedeelte <em>Netwerkgegevens</em>.</p></string8b></nlww><noww><home1 type="content"><title>Animert installeringsveiledning</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Denne animerte installeringsveiledningen viser deg hvordan du installerer og konfigurerer ditt nye HP LaserJet-produkt.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Velg produktet ditt nedenfor</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-skriverserien</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installering</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Trådløs installering</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560- og P1600-skriverserien</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB-installering</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Nettverksinstallering</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Hjem</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Installer skriverprogramvare</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Vis brukerhåndboken</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB-installering for HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Trådløs installering for HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB-installering for HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serien</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Nettverksinstallering for HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serien</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Start installeringen</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Plasser produktet i et stabilt, støvfritt område med god ventilasjon og utenfor direkte sollys.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Fjern all den oransje transportteipen og den beskyttende plasten fra produktet.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Åpne skriverkassettdekselet. Fjern skumgummiklossen, skriverkassetten, informasjonsarket og den oransje fraktlåsen. <b>MERK:</b> Resirkuler skumgummiklossen, informasjonsarket og fraktlåsen.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Fjern den oransje fraktlåsen fra enden av skriverkassetten. Roter skriverkassetten for å spre toneren jevnt. Dra i fliken for å fjerne tonerteipen. <b>MERK:</b> Resirkuler fraktlåsen og tonerteipen.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Sett skriverkassetten inn i produktet, og lukk skriverkassettdekselet.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Juster papirskinnene, og legg papir med forsiden opp i skuff 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Koble til strømledningen. <b>MERK:</b> Ta vare på modellnummeret, produktnummeret og serienummeret for å registrere produktet.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Slå på produktet.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Start programvareinstalleringen, og følg instruksjonene på skjermen.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Hvis du installerer en trådløs modell, følger du anvisningene i delen om <em>Trådløsinstallering i Windows</em> i <b>Installeringsveiledningen</b> eller delen om å <em>Installere produktet i et trådløst nettverk</em> i <b>Brukerhåndboken</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Installer utskuffen som vist her.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Installer støvdekselet.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Koble nettverkskabelen til produktet. Kontroller at én av nettverkslampene lyser på nettverksporten på baksiden av produktet.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Vent i omtrent fire minutter på at nettverket skal tildele en IP-adresse til produktet, og deretter skriver du ut en konfigurasjonsside fra kontrollpanelet på produktet. Hvis du vil skrive ut siden, trykker du på og holder nede <b>Start</b>-knappen til Klar-lampen starter å blinke. Da slipper du knappen. Finn IP-adressen i delen om <em>Nettverksinformasjon</em>.</p></string8b></noww><plww><home1 type="content"><title>Animowana podręczna instrukcja obsługi</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Ta animowana podręczna instrukcja obsługi zawiera opis sposobu instalacji i konfiguracji nowego produktu HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Poniżej wybierz produkt</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Drukarka HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalacja za pomocą złącza USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalacja bezprzewodowa</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Drukarki HP LaserJet Pro P1560 i P1600 Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalacja za pomocą złącza USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalacja sieciowa</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Strona główna</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalacja oprogramowania drukarki</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Wyświetl instrukcję obsługi</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instalacja za pomocą złącza USB drukarki HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instalacja bezprzewodowa drukarki HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instalacja za pomocą złącza USB drukarek HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instalacja sieciowa drukarek HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Rozpocznij instalację</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Do umieszczenia produktu wybierz solidne, dobrze wentylowane i pozbawione kurzu miejsce, gdzie urządzenie nie będzie wystawione na bezpośrednie działanie promieni słonecznych.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Usuń wszystkie pomarańczowe taśmy transportowe oraz plastikowy element zabezpieczający.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Otwórz drzwiczki kasety drukującej. Usuń piankę, kasetę drukującą, kartkę zabezpieczającą oraz załączoną pomarańczową blokadę transportową. <b>UWAGA:</b> Zutylizuj piankę, kartkę zabezpieczającą oraz blokadę transportową.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Usuń pomarańczową blokadę transportową z końcówki kasety drukującej. Obracaj kasetę drukującą raz do przodu raz do tyłu, aby równomiernie rozłożyć toner. Wciśnij przycisk, aby usunąć taśmę zabezpieczającą toner. <b>UWAGA:</b> Zutylizuj blokadę transportową i taśmę zabezpieczającą toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Umieść kasetę drukującą w produkcie i zamknij drzwiczki kasety drukującej.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Załaduj papier drukiem do dołu do podajnika 1 lub drukiem do góry do podajnika 2.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Podłącz przewód zasilający. <b>UWAGA:</b> Zanotuj numer modelu, numer produktu oraz numer seryjny w celu rejestracji produktu.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Włącz zasilanie urządzenia.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Uruchom oprogramowanie instalacyjne i postępuj według instrukcji wyświetlanych na ekranie.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Aby zainstalować model bezprzewodowy, zapoznaj się z informacjami w części <em>Bezprzewodowa instalacja Windows</em> w <b>Podręcznej instrukcji obsługi</b> lub w części <em>Instalacja do pracy w sieci bezprzewodowej</em> w <b>Instrukcji obsługi</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Zainstaluj pojemnik wyjściowy zgodnie z ilustracją.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Zainstaluj pokrywę zabezpieczającą przed kurzem.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Podłącz kabel sieciowy do urządzenia. Upewnij się, że zaświeciła się jedna z kontrolek sieci portu sieciowego znajdującego się z tyłu urządzenia.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Poczekaj ok. czterech minut, aby w sieci został przypisany adres IP dla danego produktu, a następnie wydrukuj stronę konfiguracji widoczną na panelu kontrolnym produktu. Aby wydrukować tę stronę, przytrzymaj wciśnięty przycisk <b>Start</b>, a następnie zwolnij przycisk, gdy zacznie migać lampka gotowości. Odszukaj adres IP w części <em>Informacje sieciowe</em>.</p></string8b></plww><ptww><home1 type="content"><title>Guia de Introdução com animação</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Este guia de introdução com animação mostra como instalar e configurar seu novo produto HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Selecione o produto abaixo</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Impressora HP LaserJet Pro Série P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalação USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalação sem fio</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Impressora HP LaserJet Pro Série P1560 e P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalação USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalação de rede</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Início</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalação do software da impressora</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Visualizar o Guia do usuário</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instalação USB da HP LaserJet Pro Série P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instalação sem fio da HP LaserJet Pro Série P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instalação USB da HP LaserJet Pro Série P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instalação de rede da HP LaserJet Pro Série P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Iniciar a instalação</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Escolha um local firme, bem ventilado, sem poeira e longe da exposição direta à luz do sol para colocar o produto.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Remova toda a fita de transporte laranja e o plástico de proteção.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Abra a porta do cartucho de impressão. Remova o bloqueio de espuma, o cartucho de impressão, a folha de conhecimento e a trava de transporte laranja afixada. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicle o bloqueio de espuma, a folha de conhecimento e a trava de transporte.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Remova a trava de transporte laranja da extremidade do cartucho de impressão. Vire a parte da frente do cartucho de impressão para trás para distribuir o toner de modo uniforme. Puxe a guia para remover a fita do toner. <b>NOTA:</b> Recicle a trava de transporte e fita do toner.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Instale o cartucho do toner no produto e feche a porta do cartucho de impressão.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Ajuste as guias de papel e carregue o papel voltado para cima na Bandeja 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Conecte o cabo de alimentação. <b>NOTA:</b> Anote o número do modelo, o número do produto e o número de série para registro do produto.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Ligue o produto.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Inicie a instalação do software e siga as instruções na tela.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Para instalar o modelo sem fio, consulte a seção <em>Instalação sem fio no Windows</em> do Guia de introdução ou consulte a<b> </b>seção <em>Instalação do produto em uma rede sem fio</em> do <b>Guia do usuário</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Instale o compartimento de saída, conforme mostrado aqui.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Instale a tampa de proteção contra pó.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Conecte o cabo de rede ao produto. Verifique se uma das luzes de rede está acesa na porta de rede localizada na parte traseira do produto.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Aguarde uns quatro minutos até que a rede atribua um endereço IP para o produto. Em seguida, imprima uma página de configuração pelo painel de controle do produto. Para imprimir a página, mantenha pressionado o botão <b>Ir</b> e solte-o quando a luz de pronto começar a piscar. Localize o endereço IP na seção <em>Informações sobre a rede</em>.</p></string8b></ptww><roww><home1 type="content"><title>Ghid de iniţiere animat</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Acest ghid de iniţiere animat prezintă modul de instalare şi configurare a noului dvs. produs HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Selectaţi mai jos produsul dvs.</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Imprimantă seria HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalaţi prin USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalaţi wireless</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Imprimantă HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalaţi prin USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Instalaţi în reţea</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Pagină de pornire</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instalaţi software-ul imprimantei</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Vizualizaţi Ghidul utilizatorului</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Instalarea imprimantei seria HP LaserJet Pro P1100 prin USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Instalarea wireless a imprimantei seria HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Instalarea imprimantei seria HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 prin USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Instalarea imprimantei seria HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 în reţea</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Începere configurare</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Pentru a amplasa produsul, alegeţi un loc stabil, bine ventilat şi fără praf, ferit de lumina directă a soarelui.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Îndepărtaţi toate benzile portocalii utilizate pentru transport şi protecţia de plastic.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Deschideţi uşa cartuşului de imprimare. Scoateţi blocul din polistiren, cartuşul de imprimare, fişa de instrucţiuni şi dispozitivul portocaliu de blocare la transport. <b>NOTĂ:</b> Reciclaţi blocul din polistiren, fişa de instrucţiuni şi dispozitivul de blocare la transport.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Scoateţi dispozitivul portocaliu de blocare la transport din capătul cartuşului de imprimare. Rotiţi cartuşul de imprimare în faţă şi în spate pentru a distribui uniform tonerul. Trageţi capătul pentru a înlătura banda tonerului. <b>NOTĂ:</b> Reciclaţi dispozitivul de blocare la transport şi banda tonerului.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Instalaţi cartuşul de imprimare în produs şi apoi închideţi uşa cartuşului de imprimare.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Reglaţi ghidajele pentru hârtie şi încărcaţi hârtia cu faţa în sus în tava 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Conectaţi cablul de alimentare. <b>NOTĂ:</b> Notaţi numărul modelului, numărul produsului şi numărul de serie pentru înregistrarea produsului.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Porniţi produsul.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Începeţi instalarea software-ul şi urmaţi instrucţiunile de pe ecran.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Pentru a instala un model wireless, consultaţi secţiunea <em>Instalarea wireless pe Windows</em> din <b>Ghidul de instalare</b> sau consultaţi secţiunea <em>Instalarea produsului într-o reţea wireless</em> din <b>Ghidul utilizatorului</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Instalaţi sertarul de ieşire conform ilustraţiei.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Instalaţi capacul antipraf.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Conectaţi cablul de reţea la produs. Verificaţi dacă este aprins unul dintre ledurile de reţea de la portul de reţea aflat în partea din spate a produsului.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Aşteptaţi aproximativ patru minute pentru ca reţeaua să atribuie produsului o adresă IP şi apoi imprimaţi o pagină de configurare de la panoul de control al produsului. Pentru a imprima pagina, apăsaţi şi menţineţi apăsat butonul <b>Accesare</b>, apoi eliberaţi-l când ledul Pregătit începe să clipească. Localizaţi adresa IP în secţiunea <em>Informaţii despre reţea</em>.</p></string8b></roww><ruww><home1 type="content"><title>Руководство по началу работы (с использованием анимации)</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Данное анимированное руководство по началу работы поможет выполнить установку и настройку ПО нового принтера HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Выберите используемое устройство</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Серия HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Установка с USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Беспроводная установка</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Серии HP LaserJet Pro P1560 и P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Установка с USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Установка по сети</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Главная</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Установка программного обеспечения принтера</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Просмотр руководства пользователя</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Установка с USB для серии принтеров HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Установка через беспроводное подключение для серии принтеров HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Установка с USB для серий принтеров HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Установка по сети для серий принтеров HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Начать установку</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Выберите для установки устройства хорошо проветриваемое непыльное помещение и не допускайте попадания прямых солнечных лучей на устройство.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Уберите все оранжевые упаковочные ленты и защитные пленки.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Откройте дверцу картриджа печати. Уберите пенопласт, картридж печати, верхний лист и оранжевый транспортировочный фиксатор. <b>ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ.</b> Утилизируйте пенопласт, верхний лист и транспортировочный фиксатор.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Снимите оранжевый транспортировочный фиксатор с картриджа печати. Покачайте картридж вперед-назад для равномерного распределения тонера. Чтобы удалить ленту тонера, потяните за выступ. <b>ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ.</b> Утилизируйте транспортировочный фиксатор и ленту тонера.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Вставьте картридж с тонером в устройство и закройте дверцу доступа к картриджу печати.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Отрегулируйте направляющие бумаги и загрузите бумагу лицевой стороной вверх в лоток 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Подсоединение шнура питания. <b>ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ.</b> Запишите номер модели, номер изделия и серийный номер для регистрации устройства.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Включите устройство.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Запустите установку ПО и следуйте инструкциям на экране.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Для установки ПО беспроводных моделей см. раздел <em>Беспроводная установка в Windows</em> в <b>Руководстве по началу работы</b> или раздел <em>Установка устройства в беспроводной сети</em> в <b>Руководстве пользователя</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Установите выходной приемник, как показано здесь.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Установите крышку.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Подключите сетевой кабель к устройству. Убедитесь, что светится один из индикаторов на сетевом порте устройства, расположенном на его задней стороне.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Подождите примерно четыре минуты, пока устройству будет присвоен IP-адрес, затем распечатайте страницу конфигурации с панели управления устройства. Чтобы распечатать страницу, удерживайте кнопку <b>Go</b> (Пуск) пока не замигает индикатор готовности. Найдите IP-адрес в разделе <em>Сведения о сети</em>.</p></string8b></ruww><skww><home1 type="content"><title>Animovaná úvodná príručka</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Táto animovaná úvodná príručka vám ukáže, ako nainštalovať a nastaviť nové zariadenie HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Nižšie vyberte svoje zariadenie</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Séria tlačiarní HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB inštalácia</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Bezdrôtová inštalácia</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Séria tlačiarní HP LaserJet Pro P1560 a P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB inštalácia</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Sieťová inštalácia</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Domov</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Inštalácia softvéru k tlačiarni</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Zobraziť používateľskú príručku</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB inštalácia série HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Bezdrôtová inštalácia série HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB inštalácia série HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Sieťová inštalácia série HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Začať inštaláciu</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Produkt umiestnite na stabilnom, dobre vetranom a bezprašnom mieste, na ktoré nedopadá priame slnečné svetlo.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Odstráňte všetky kúsky oranžovej prepravnej pásky a ochranný plast.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Otvorte dvierka tlačovej kazety. Vyberte penový blok, tlačovú kazetu, informačný hárok a osadenú oranžovú prepravnú zámku. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Recyklujte penový blok, informačný hárok a prepravnú zámku.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Z konca tlačovej kazety odstráňte oranžovú prepravnú zámku. Otáčaním kazety spredu dozadu zabezpečte rovnomerné rozloženie tonera. Pásku tonera stiahnite po uchopení za okraj. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Prepravnú zámku a pásku z tonera recyklujte.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Kazetu s tonerom nainštalujte do zariadenia a zavrite dvierka na vloženie kazety.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Nastavte vodiace lišty papiera a papier vložte lícovou stranou nahor do zásobníka 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Pripojte napájací kábel. <b>POZNÁMKA:</b> Poznačte si číslo modelu, číslo produktu a sériové číslo. Použijete ich pri registrácii produktu.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Zapnite produkt.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Spustite inštaláciu softvéru a postupujte podľa pokynov na obrazovke.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Ak chcete nainštalovať model s bezdrôtovým rozhraním, pozrite si časť <em>Inštalácia bezdrôtového rozhrania v systéme Windows</em> v <b>úvodnej príručke</b> alebo časť <em>Inštalácia zariadenia v rámci bezdrôtovej siete</em> v <b>používateľskej príručke</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Výstupnú priehradku nainštalujte podľa znázornených pokynov.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Nainštalujte prachový kryt.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>K zariadeniu pripojte sieťový kábel. Skontrolujte, či svieti jeden zo sieťových indikátorov na sieťovom porte nachádzajúcom sa na zadnej časti produktu.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Čakajte približne štyri minúty, kým sieť nepridelí zariadeniu IP adresu. Potom vytlačte konfiguračnú stránku zariadenia z ovládacieho panelu. Ak chcete vytlačiť stránku, stlačte a podržte tlačidlo <b>Go</b> (Choď) a potom keď kontrola pripraveného stavu začne blikať tlačidlo uvoľnite. IP adresu vyhľadajte v časti <em>Informácie o sieti</em>.</p></string8b></skww><slww><home1 type="content"><title>Animirani priročnik za začetek uporabe</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Animirani priročnik za začetek uporabe prikazuje postopek namestitev in nastavitve izdelka HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Spodaj izberite svoj izdelek</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Serija tiskalnikov HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Namestitev na vrata USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Brezžična namestitev</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Seriji tiskalnikov HP LaserJet Pro P1560 in P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Namestitev na vrata USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Omrežna namestitev</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Na začetek</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Namestitev programske opreme tiskalnika</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Prikaz uporabniškega priročnika</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Namestitev izdelka serije HP LaserJet Pro P1100 na vrata USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Brezžična namestitev izdelka serije HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Namestitev izdelka serije HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 na vrata USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Omrežna namestitev izdelka serije HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Začetek nastavljanja</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Za postavitev izdelka izberite trden, dobro prezračevan in čist prostor, ki ni izpostavljen neposredni sončni svetlobi.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Odstranite ves oranžni zaščitni trak in zaščitno folijo.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Odprite vratca tiskalne kartuše. Odstranite peno, tiskalno kartušo, zaščitni list in nameščeni oranžen transportni zaklep. <b>OPOMBA:</b> peno, zaščitni list in transportni zaklep reciklirajte.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Odstranite transportni zaklep, ki je na koncu tiskalne kartuše. Tiskalno kartušo zasukajte naprej in nazaj, da enakomerno porazdelite toner. Povlecite jeziček, da odstranite trak tonerja. <b>OPOMBA:</b> transportni zaklep in trak tonerja reciklirajte.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Kartušo s tonerjem namestite v izdelek in zaprite vratca tiskalne kartuše.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Prilagodite vodila za papir in naložite papir z licem navzgor na pladenj 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Priključite napajalni kabel. <b>OPOMBA:</b> zabeležite si številko modela, številko izdelka in serijsko številko za poznejšo registracijo izdelka.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Vklopite izdelek.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Zaženite namestitev programske opreme in sledite navodilom na zaslonu.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Za namestitev brezžičnega modela si oglejte razdelek <em>Brezžična namestitev v sistemu Windows</em> v <b>Priročniku za začetek uporabe</b> ali razdelek <em>Namestitev izdelka v brezžično omrežje</em> v <b>Uporabniškem priročniku</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Namestite izhodni predal, kot je prikazano.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Namestite protiprašni pokrov.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Omrežni kabel priključite na izdelek. Preverite, ali sveti ena od lučk omrežja na omrežnih vratih na hrbtni strani izdelka.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Počakajte približno štiri minute, da omrežje izdelku dodeli naslov IP, in nato prek nadzorne plošče izdelka natisnite konfiguracijsko stran. Stran natisnete tako, da pritisnete in držite gumb <b>Pojdi</b> in ga spustite, ko začne utripati lučka pripravljenosti. V razdelku <em>Network Information</em> (Podatki o omrežju) poiščite naslov IP.</p></string8b></slww><srww><home1 type="content"><title>Animirani priručnik za početak rada</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Ovaj animirani priručnik za početak rada pokazuje vam kako da instalirate i podesite svoj novi HP LaserJet štampač.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Izaberite proizvod u nastavku</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Printer serija</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>»USB instaliranje</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Bežično instaliranje</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 i P1600 Printer serija</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>»USB instaliranje</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Mrežno instaliranje</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Početna stranica</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Instaliranje softvera štampača</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Prikaz uputstva za upotrebu</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>USB instaliranje HP LaserJet Pro P1100 serije</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Bežično instaliranje HP LaserJet Pro P1100 serije</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>USB instaliranje HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 serije</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Mrežno instaliranje HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 serije</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Pokreni instalaciju</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Uređaj postavite na stabilnu podlogu u prostoriji sa dobrom ventilacijom i bez prašine, udaljen od direktne sunčeve svetlosti.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>U potpunosti uklonite narandžastu traku za pakovanje i zaštitnu plastiku.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Otvorite vratanca kasete sa tonerom. Uklonite blokadu od pene, kasetu sa tonerom, list za detekciju i postavljenu narandžastu bravu za transport. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Reciklirajte blokadu od pene, list za detekciju i bravu za transport.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Uklonite narandžastu bravu za transport sa kraja kasete sa tonerom. Okrenite kasetu sa tonerom napred-nazad da biste ravnomerno rasporedili toner. Povucite isečak da biste uklonili traku tonera. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Reciklirajte bravu za transport i traku tonera.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Stavite kasetu sa tonerom u proizvod i zatvorite vratanca za kasetu sa tonerom.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Podesite vođice papira i stavite papir licem nagore u ležište 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Priključite kabl za napajanje. <b>NAPOMENA:</b> Zabeležite broj modela, broj proizvoda i serijski broj za registraciju proizvoda.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Uključite uređaj.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Pokrenite instalaciju softvera i pratite uputstva na ekranu.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Da biste instalirali bežični model, pogledajte odeljak <em>Bežična instalacija za Windows</em> u <b>priručniku za početak rada</b>, odnosno pogledajte odeljak <em>Instaliranje uređaja u bežičnoj mreži</em> u <b>uputstvu za upotrebu</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Postavite izlaznu korpu kao što ovde prikazano.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Postavite poklopac protiv prašine.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Priključite mrežni kabl u proizvod. Proverite da li jedna od lampica za mrežu svetli na mrežnom priključku koji se nalazi na zadnjoj strani uređaja.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Sačekajte oko četiri minuta da bi mreža dodelila IP adresu uređaju, a zatim odštampajte stranicu sa konfiguracijom iz kontrolne table uređaja. Da biste odštampali stranicu, pritisnite i zadržite dugme <b>Go</b> (Idi), a zatim pustite dugme kada lampica spremnosti počne da trepće. Pronađite IP adresu u odeljku <em>Informacije o mreži</em>.</p></string8b></srww><svww><home1 type="content"><title>Animerad starthandbok</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Den här animerade starthandboken visar hur du installerar och konfigurerar din nya HP LaserJet-produkt.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Välj din produkt nedan</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 skrivarserie</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installera USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Trådlös installation</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 och P1600 skrivarserie</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installera USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Installation i nätverk</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Hem</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Installera skrivarprogramvara</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Visa användarhandbok</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien - installera USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100-serien - trådlös installation</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serien - installera USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600-serien - installation i nätverk</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Påbörja installationen</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Placera produkten i ett välventilerat, dammfritt utrymme och fritt från direkt solljus.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Avlägsna all orange förpackningstejp och skyddsplast.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Öppna tonerkassettluckan. Ta bort skumplasten, tonerkassetten, pappersarket och det fästa orangefärgade transportlåset. <b>Obs!</b> Återvinn skumplasten, pappersarket och transportlåset.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Ta bort det orangefärgade transportlåset från tonerkassettens ände. Rotera tonerkassetten fram och tillbaka så att tonern fördelas jämnt. Ta bort tonertejpen genom att dra i fliken. <b>Obs!</b> Återvinn transportlåset och tonertejpen.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Sätt i tonerkassetten i produkten och stäng sedan tonerkassettluckan.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Justera pappersledarna och lägg i papper med framsidan vänd uppåt i fack 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Anslut nätsladden. <b>Obs!</b> Anteckna modellnummer, produktnummer och serienummer för produktregistrering.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Starta produkten.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Starta programinstallationen och följ anvisningarna på skärmen.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Mer information om hur du installerar en trådlös modell finns i avsnittet <em>Trådlös Windows-installation</em> i <b>Starthandboken</b> eller i avsnittet <em>Installera produkten i ett trådlöst nätverk</em> i <b>Användarhandboken</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Sätt i utmatningsfacket enligt bilden.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Installera dammskyddet.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Anslut nätverkskabeln till produkten. Kontrollera att någon av nätverkslamporna lyser på nätverksporten på produktens baksida.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Vänta i ca fyra minuter på att nätverket ska tilldela produkten en IP-adress och skriv sedan ut en konfigurationssida från produktens kontrollpanel. Skriv ut sidan genom att hålla knappen <b>Go</b> intryckt och sedan släppa upp den när klarlampan börjar blinka. Leta reda på IP-adressen i avsnittet <em>Nätverksinformation</em>.</p></string8b></svww><thww><home1 type="content"><title>คู่มือการเริ่มต้นใช้งานแบบภาพเคลื่อนไหว</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>คู่มือการเริ่มต้นใช้งานแบบภาพเคลื่อนไหวนี้จะแสดงวิธีการติดตั้งและตั้งค่าเครื่องพิมพ์ HP LaserJet ใหม่ของคุณ</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>เลือกเครื่องพิมพ์ของคุณด้านล่าง</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>เครื่องพิมพ์ HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» ติดตั้ง USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» ติดตั้งไร้สาย</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>เครื่องพิมพ์ HP LaserJet Pro P1560 และ P1600 Series</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» ติดตั้ง USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» ติดตั้งเครือข่าย</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» หน้าแรก</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» ติดตั้งซอฟต์แวร์เครื่องพิมพ์</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» ดูคู่มือผู้ใช้</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series ติดตั้ง USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series ติดตั้งไร้สาย</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series ติดตั้ง USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series ติดตั้งเครือข่าย</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» เริ่มการติดตั้ง</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>เลือกวางเครื่องพิมพ์ในบริเวณที่แข็งแรง อากาศถ่ายเทสะดวก และไม่ถูกแสงแดดโดยตรง</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>แกะเทปสีส้มและพลาสติกป้องกันทั้งหมดออก</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>เปิดช่องใส่ตลับหมึกพิมพ์ นำโฟม, ตลับหมึกพิมพ์, แผ่นการค้นหา และตัวล็อคสีส้มที่ใช้ในการขนส่งออก <b>หมายเหตุ:</b> รีไซเคิลโฟม, แผ่นการค้นหา และตัวล็อคที่ใช้ในการขนส่ง</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>ดึงตัวล็อคสีส้มที่ใช้ในการขนส่งออกจากปลายของตลับหมึกพิมพ์ หมุนตลับหมึกพิมพ์จากด้านหน้าไปด้านหลังเพื่อกระจายหมึกพิมพ์ให้เท่ากัน ดึงแท็บเพื่อดึงเทปผงหมึกออก <b>หมายเหตุ:</b> รีไซเคิลตัวล็อคที่ใช้ในการขนส่งและเทปผงหมึก</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>ใส่ตลับผงหมึกเข้าไปในเครื่องพิมพ์ แล้วปิดฝาช่องใส่ตลับหมึกพิมพ์</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>ปรับตัวกั้นกระดาษและใส่กระดาษคว่ำหน้าลงในถาด 1</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>เสียบสายไฟ <b>หมายเหตุ:</b> บันทึกหมายเลขรุ่น หมายเลขเครื่องพิมพ์ และหมายเลขผลิตภัณฑ์สำหรับการลงทะเบียนเครื่องพิมพ์</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>เปิดเครื่องพิมพ์</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>เริ่มต้นการติดตั้งซอฟต์แวร์ และทำตามคำแนะนำบนหน้าจอ</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>ในการติดตั้งรุ่นไร้สาย โปรดดูที่ส่วน <em>การติดตั้งแบบไร้สายสำหรับ Windows</em> ใน <b>คู่มือการเริ่มต้นใช้งาน</b> หรือดูที่ส่วน <em>ติดตั้งเครื่องพิมพ์บนเครือข่ายแบบใช้สาย</em> ใน <b>คู่มือผู้ใช้</b> </wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>ติดตั้งถาดกระดาษออกดังที่แสดงที่นี่</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>ติดตั้งฝาปิดป้องกันฝุ่น</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>เชื่อมต่อสายเคเบิลเครือข่ายกับผลิตภัณฑ์ ตรวจสอบว่ามีไฟเครือข่ายสว่างขึ้นที่พอร์ตเครือข่ายที่ด้านหลังของเครื่องพิมพ์</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>รอประมาณสี่นาทีเพื่อให้เครือข่ายกำหนด IP แอดเดรสสำหรับเครื่องพิมพ์ แล้วพิมพ์หน้าการกำหนดค่าจากแผงควบคุมของเครื่องพิมพ์ ในการพิมพ์หน้าดังกล่าว ให้กดปุ่ม <b>ไป</b> ค้างไว้ แล้วปล่อยปุ่มเมื่อไฟพร้อมเริ่มกะพริบ ค้นหา IP แอดเดรสในส่วน <em>ข้อมูลเครือข่าย</em> </p></string8b></thww><trww><home1 type="content"><title>Animasyonlu Başlangıç Kılavuzu</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Bu animasyonlu başlangıç kılavuzu yeni HP LaserJet ürününüzün nasıl kurulacağını ve ayarlanacağını gösterir.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Aşağıda ürününüzü seçin</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Yazıcı Serisi</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB yüklemesi</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Kablosuz yüklemesi</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 ve P1600 Yazıcı Serisi</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB yüklemesi</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Ağ yüklemesi</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Giriş Sayfası</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Yazıcı Yazılımını Yükle</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Kullanım Kılavuzunu Görüntüle</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series USB yüklemesi</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 Series kablosuz yüklemesi</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series USB yüklemesi</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 Series ağ yüklemesi</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Ayarlamayı Başlat</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Ürünü yerleştirmek için, sağlam, iyi havalanan, tozsuz, güneş görmeyen bir yer seçin.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Tüm turuncu nakliye bantlarını ve koruyucu plastiği çıkarın.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Yazıcı kartuşu kapağını açın. Köpük koruyucuyu, yazıcı kartuşunu, tanıtma sayfasını ve takılı turuncu nakliye kilidini çıkartın. <b>NOT:</b> Köpük koruyucuyu, tanıtma sayfasını ve nakliye kilidini geri dönüşüme verin.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Yazıcı kartuşunun ucundaki turuncu renkli nakliye kilidini çıkarın. Toneri eşit olarak dağıtmak için yazıcı kartuşunu önden arkaya doğru döndürün. Toner bandını çıkarmak için şeridi çekin. <b>NOT:</b> Nakliye kilidini ve toner bandını geri dönüşüme verin.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Toner kartuşunu ürüne takın ve yazıcı kartuşu kapağını kapatın.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Kağıt kılavuzlarını ayarlayın ve kağıdı ön yüzü yukarı gelecek şekilde Tepsi 1'e yerleştirin.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Elektrik kablosunu prize takın. <b>NOT:</b> Ürün kaydı için model numarasını, ürün numarasını ve seri numarasını not alın.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Ürünü çalıştırın.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Yazılım yüklemesini başlatın ve ekrandaki yönergeleri uygulayın.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Kablosuz bir modeli yüklemek için, <b>Başlangıç Kılavuzu</b>'ndaki <em>Windows Kablosuz Yüklemesi</em> bölümüne veya <b>Kullanım Kılavuzu</b>'ndaki <em>Ürünü kablosuz ağa yükleme</em> bölümüne başvurun.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Çıkış bölmesini burada gösterildiği şekilde takın.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Toz kapağını takın.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Ağ kablosunu ürüne bağlayın. Ürünün arka bölümünde bulunan ağ bağlantı noktasındaki ağ ışıklarından birinin yandığından emin olun.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Ağın aygıta bir IP adresi ataması için dört dakika kadar bekleyin ve sonra ürünün kontrol panelinden bir yapılandırma sayfası yazdırın. Sayfayı yazdırmak için, <b>Git</b> düğmesini basılı tutun ve hazır ışığı yanıp sönmeye başladığında parmağınızı düğmeden çekin. IP adresini, <em>Ağ Bilgileri</em> bölümünden bulun.</p></string8b></trww><ukww><home1 type="content"><title>Анімований короткий посібник користувача</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>У цьому анімованому короткому посібнику користувача пояснюється, як встановлювати та налаштовувати новий пристрій HP LaserJet.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Виберіть потрібний пристрій нижче</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Серія принтерів HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Встановлення через USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Встановлення через бездротову мережу</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Серія принтерів HP LaserJet Pro P1560 і P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Встановлення через USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Встановлення через мережу</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Головна</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Встановити ПЗ принтера</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Переглянути посібник користувача</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Встановлення HP LaserJet Pro P1100 через USB</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Встановлення HP LaserJet Pro P1100 через бездротову мережу</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Встановлення HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 через USB</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Встановлення HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 через мережу</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Почати налаштування</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Для розміщення пристрою виберіть надійне та чисте місце, яке добре провітрюється та захищене від прямих сонячних променів.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Зніміть усі оранжеві транспортувальні стрічки і захисну плівку.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Відкрийте кришку доступу до картриджів. Вийміть пінопластовий блок, картридж, аркуш із покроковими вказівками щодо встановлення і оранжевий транспортувальний фіксатор. <b>ПРИМІТКА.</b> Пінопластовий блок, аркуш із покроковими вказівками і транспортувальний фіксатор слід віддати на повторну переробку.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Зніміть оранжевий транспортувальний фіксатор з краю картриджа. Кілька разів оберніть картридж уперед і назад, щоб рівномірно розподілити у ньому тонер. Потягніть вкладку, щоб зняти плівку з картриджа. <b>ПРИМІТКА.</b> Транспортувальний фіксатор і плівку картриджа слід віддати на повторну переробку.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Установіть картридж у виріб і закрийте кришку доступу до картриджів.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Відрегулюйте напрямні для паперу і завантажте папір лицьовою стороною догори в лоток 1.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Підключіть шнур живлення. <b>ПРИМІТКА.</b> Запишіть номер моделі, номер виробу і серійний номер для реєстрації виробу.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Увімкніть виріб.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Установіть програмне забезпечення і виконайте вказівки на екрані.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Щоб установити бездротову модель, читайте розділ <em>Встановлення через бездротову мережу у системі Windows</em> у <b>короткому посібнику користувача</b>, або читайте розділ <em>Встановлення виробу через бездротову мережу</em> у <b>посібнику користувача</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Встановіть вихідний відсік, як показано тут.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Встановіть захист від пилу.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Підключіть мережевий кабель до принтера. Перевірте, чи світиться один з індикаторів мережі біля мережевого порту позаду пристрою.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Зачекайте близько чотирьох хвилин, щоб мережею було призначено ІР-адресу для виробу, а тоді надрукуйте сторінку конфігурації з панелі керування виробу. Щоб надрукувати сторінку, натисніть і утримуйте кнопку <b>Go</b> (Перейти), а тоді відпустіть кнопку, коли почне миготіти індикатор готовності. Знайдіть потрібну IP-адресу у розділі <em>Мережева інформація</em>.</p></string8b></ukww><viww><home1 type="content"><title>Hướng dẫn Bắt đầu Sử dụng bằng Hoạt ảnh</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>Hướng dẫn bắt đầu sử dụng bằng hoạt ảnh này sẽ chỉ cách cài đặt và thiết lập máy in HP LaserJet mới của bạn.</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>Chọn máy in bên dưới</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>Dòng Máy in HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Cài đặt USB</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Cài đặt không dây</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>Dòng Máy in HP LaserJet P1560 và P1600</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» Cài đặt USB</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» Cài đặt mạng</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» Trang chủ</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» Cài đặt phần mềm máy in</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» Xem Hướng dẫn Sử dụng</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>Cài đặt USB Dòng HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>Cài đặt không dây Dòng HP LaserJet Pro P1100</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>Cài đặt USB Dòng HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>Cài đặt mạng Dòng HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» Bắt đầu Cài đặt</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>Chọn nơi vững chắc, được thông hơi tốt, không có bụi bặm, không tiếp xúc trực tiếp với ánh sáng mặt trời để đặt sản phẩm.</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>Tháo tất cả băng vận chuyển màu da cam và lớp bảo vệ bằng nhựa.</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>Mở nắp hộp mực in. Tháo lớp đệm xốp, hộp mực in, tờ thông tin và khóa vận chuyển màu da cam được kèm theo. <b>LƯU Ý:</b> Có thể tái chế lớp đệm xốp, tờ thông tin và khóa vận chuyển.</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>Tháo khóa vận chuyển màu da cam ra khỏi đáy hộp mực in. Xoay ngược hộp mực in từ đằng trước ra đằng sau để rải đều bột mực. Kéo đầu để tháo dải băng mực. <b>LƯU Ý:</b> Có thể tái chế khóa vận chuyển và dải băng mực.</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>Lắp hộp bột mực vào sản phẩm, rồi đóng nắp hộp mực in.</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>Điều chỉnh các thiết bị dẫn giấy và nạp giấy vào Khay 1 với mặt quay lên.</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>Cắm dây nguồn vào. <b>LƯU Ý:</b> Ghi lại số kiểu máy, số sản phẩm và số sê-ri để đăng ký sản phẩm.</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>Bật sản phẩm.</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>Bắt đầu cài đặt phần mềm và thực hiện theo hướng dẫn trên màn hình.</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>Để cài đặt kiểu không dây, hãy tham khảo phần <em>Cài đặt không dây trên Windows</em> trong <b>Hướng dẫn Bắt đầu Sử dụng</b>, hoặc tham khảo phần <em>Cài đặt sản phẩm trên mạng không dây</em> trong <b>Hướng dẫn Sử dụng</b>.</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>Lắp ngăn giấy ra như hình minh họa dưới đây.</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>Lắp tấm che bụi.</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>Cắm cáp mạng vào sản phẩm. Kiểm tra xem một trong các đèn mạng bật sáng trên cổng mạng ở phía sau sản phẩm.</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>Chờ khoảng bốn phút để mạng gán địa chỉ IP cho sản phẩm, sau đó in trang cấu hình từ bảng điều khiển của sản phẩm. Để in trang này, hãy bấm và giữ phím <b>Go</b> (Bắt đầu), sau đó thả nút ra khi đèn sẵn sàng bắt đầu nhấp nháy. Tìm địa chỉ IP trong phần <em>Thông tin Mạng</em>.</p></string8b></viww><zhcn><home1 type="content"><title>动画入门指南</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>此动画入门指南演示如何安装和设置您的新 HP LaserJet 产品。</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><em>在下面选择您的产品</em></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 打印机系列</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 安装</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 无线安装</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 和 P1600 打印机系列</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 安装</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 网络安装</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» 主页</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» 安装打印机软件</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» 查看用户指南</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 系列 USB 安装</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 系列无线安装</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 系列 USB 安装</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 系列网络安装</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» 开始安装</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>选择一个稳固、通风良好、无尘且远离直射日光的区域放置产品。</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>撕下所有橙色装运胶带和塑料保护膜。</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>打开打印碳粉盒挡盖。 取出泡沫块、打印碳粉盒、包装纸以及随附的橙色装运锁。 <b>注：</b> 回收泡沫块、包装纸及装运锁。</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>从打印碳粉盒一端取下橙色装运锁。 从前到后旋转打印碳粉盒，以使碳粉分布均匀。 拉动拉环撕下碳粉胶带。 <b>注：</b> 回收装运锁和碳粉胶带。</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>将碳粉盒装入产品中，然后合上打印碳粉盒挡盖。</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>调整纸张导板，将纸张正面朝上装入纸盘 1。</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>插入电源线。 <b>注：</b> 记下型号、产品号及序列号，以便注册产品。</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>打开产品电源。</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>开始安装软件，然后按照屏幕上的说明操作。</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>要安装无线机型，请参阅<b>《入门指南》</b>中的 <em>Windows 无线安装</em>部分，或者参阅<b>《用户指南》</b>中的<em>在无线网络上安装产品</em>部分。</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>如图所示安装出纸槽。</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>安装防尘盖。</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>将网络电缆连接到产品。 检查位于产品背面的网络端口上的其中一个网络指示灯是否亮起。</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>等待四分钟，让网络为产品分配 IP 地址，然后从产品控制面板打印配置页。 要打印页面，请按住<b>执行</b>按钮，然后在就绪指示灯开始闪烁时松开按钮。 在 <em>Network Information</em>（网络信息）部分找到 IP 地址。</p></string8b></zhcn><zhtw><home1 type="content"><title>動畫入門指南</title></home1><home2 type="content"><p>本動畫入門指南會示範如何安裝及設定新的 HP LaserJet 產品。</p></home2><selectProd type="content"><p><b>請於下方選擇您的產品</b></p></selectProd><series1Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 印表機系列</prodName></series1Name><prod1aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 安裝</mainButt></prod1aButt><prod1bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 無線安裝</mainButt></prod1bButt><series2Name type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560 和 P1600 印表機系列</prodName></series2Name><prod2aButt type="content"><mainButt>» USB 安裝</mainButt></prod2aButt><prod2bButt type="content"><mainButt>» 網路安裝</mainButt></prod2bButt><topButt1 type="content"><topButt>» 首頁</topButt></topButt1><topButt2 type="content"><topButt>» 安裝印表機軟體</topButt></topButt2><topButt3 type="content"><topButt>» 檢視使用指南</topButt></topButt3><prod1aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 系列 USB 安裝</prodName></prod1aName><prod1bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1100 系列無線安裝</prodName></prod1bName><prod2aName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 系列 USB 安裝</prodName></prod2aName><prod2bName type="content"><prodName>HP LaserJet Pro P1560/P1600 系列網路安裝</prodName></prod2bName><begin type="content"><beginButt>» 開始設定</beginButt></begin><!--CICADA USB / COMMON--><string1 type="content"><p>請選擇一個平整穩固、通風良好且沒有灰塵的區域放置本產品，並避免陽光直射。</p></string1><string2 type="content"><p>將所有橘色裝運膠帶和保護塑膠套移除。</p></string2><string3 type="content"><p>打開碳粉匣擋門。取下泡棉板、碳粉匣、探索表，以及附加的橘色裝運固定鎖。<b>註：</b>請回收泡棉板、碳粉匣、探索表和裝運固定鎖。</p></string3><string4 type="content"><p>從碳粉匣末端取下橘色裝運固定鎖。將碳粉匣前後轉一轉，使碳粉分佈均勻。拉出標籤，取下碳粉膠帶。<b>註：</b>請回收裝運固定鎖和碳粉膠帶。</p></string4><string5 type="content"><p>將碳粉匣裝回產品中，然後關上碳粉匣擋門。</p></string5><string6 type="content"><p>調整紙張導板，將紙張列印面向上裝入 1 號紙匣。</p></string6><string7 type="content"><p>插入電源線。<b>註：</b>請記下型號、產品號碼、序號，產品註冊時需要這些資訊。</p></string7><string8 type="content"><p>開啟本產品電源。</p></string8><string9 type="content"><p>啟動軟體安裝，然後按照畫面上的指示進行。</p></string9><!--CICADA WIRELESS--><string10 type="content"><wireless>若要安裝無線機型，請參閱《<b>入門指南</b>》中的「<b>Windows 無線安裝</b>」一節，或參閱《<b>使用指南</b>》中的「<b>在無線網路上安裝本產品</b>」一節。</wireless></string10><!--MANTIS USB--><string5a type="content"><p>依照此處所示，裝上出紙槽。</p></string5a><string5b type="content"><p>安裝防塵蓋。</p></string5b><!--MANTIS NW--><string8a type="content"><p>將網路線連接到產品。確認產品背後網路連接埠上的其中一個網路指示燈亮起。</p></string8a><string8b type="content"><p>等候四分鐘左右，待網路指派本產品的 IP 位址，然後從產品控制面板列印組態頁。要列印該頁，請按住<b>執行</b>按鈕，待就緒指示燈開始閃爍時再放開按鈕。在「<b>網路資訊</b>」區段中找到 IP 位址。</p></string8b></zhtw></document>